<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources><string name="110000">The Fifth-Fold Mystery</string>
<string name="110001">You have entered the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see the Sleeping Man and have no further need of his Five-Fold Mysteries.</string>
<string name="110002">Sensei Dharvana is dead and her Five-Fold Mysteries with her. You may pursue them further but only for your own enlightenment.</string>
<string name="110003">The First-Fold Mystery</string>
<string name="110004">The Fourth-Fold Mystery</string>
<string name="110005">Before Sensei Dharvana will let anyone enter her temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum, they must recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man. The Fourth-Fold Mystery is &quot;Who did he seek?&quot;

You have learned the Mystery from Arden Swift in the Hellbreath Tavern, who claims the Sleeping Man sought a creature called the Knower of Places.</string>
<string name="110006">The Puzzlers&apos; Sepulcher</string>
<string name="110007">You can feel yourself getting closer to the hidden lair of the Knower of Places. In a secret chamber deep in the icy wastes of Cania, you have found the statue of a gargoyle. Etched along its base are the words &quot;Stone to stone the stone turns; Lightning to lightning, the lightning fades.&quot;</string>
<string name="110008">You have killed the Scrivener, a small dog-like beast that you found whining at the entrance to a cave at the heart of town. It seems he alone held the secret to dispelling the magical force that continues to block the cavern&apos;s entrance. It would seem the secret has died with him.</string>
<string name="110009">The Second-Fold Mystery</string>
<string name="110010">The Third-Fold Mystery</string>
<string name="110011">Before Sensei Dharvana will let you enter her temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see the Sleeping Man, she wants you to learn and recite his Five-Fold Mysteries. The Third-Fold Mystery of the Sleeping Man is &quot;Why did he leave?&quot;</string>
<string name="110012">Before Sensei Dharvana will let you enter her temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see the Sleeping Man, she wants you to learn and recite his Five-Fold Mysteries. The Third-Fold Mystery of the Sleeping Man is &quot;Why did he leave?&quot;

You learned the Mystery from the Spirits of the Dead who call the City of Lost Souls their home. They claim that the Sleeping Man&apos;s heart had known no love.</string>
<string name="110013">Before Sensei Dharvana will let anyone enter her temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum, they must recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man. The Third-Fold Mystery is &quot;Why did he leave?&quot;

You learned the Mystery from the Githzerai Pilgrims now trapped in Cania. They claim that the Sleeping Man&apos;s heart had known no love.
</string>
<string name="110014">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Arden Swift, the jester you met in the Hellbreath Tavern in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Caddisthwaite the Doomed.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced him to give you all his winnings from the card tricks and gambling sessions he plays with the tavern&apos;s patrons.</string>
<string name="110015">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Arden Swift, the jester you met in the Hellbreath Tavern in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Caddisthwaite the Doomed.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced him to pick a fight with the tavernkeeper, a powerful Shadow Dragon.</string>
<string name="110016">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Arden Swift, the jester you met in the Hellbreath Tavern in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Caddisthwaite the Doomed.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently made him promise to write an epic song about your exploits and spread your fame throughout the planes.</string>
<string name="110017">Arden Swift, the jester you met in the Hellbreath Tavern in the City of Lost Souls, is now dead. It appears he ultimately lived up to his True Name: Caddisthwaite the Doomed. As a result, the name is of little use to you anymore.</string>
<string name="110018">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.</string>
<string name="110019">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to resist the temptations of your nemesis Mephistopheles when you faced each other amidst the ruins of Waterdeep.</string>
<string name="110020">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to put aside the feelings of guilt she still harbored regarding her betrayal of the city of Neverwinter.</string>
<string name="110021">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to set aside her paladinhood and embrace the path of evil.</string>
<string name="110022">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to set aside her evil ways and once again pursue her long-forgotten paladinhood.</string>
<string name="110023">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to surrender her soul to you that you might be better able to face your nemesis, Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110024">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to love you despite your various flaws of character.</string>
<string name="110025">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Lady Aribeth de Tylmarande. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Va&apos;ardalia the Twinsouled.

You recently sold her name to Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss, condemning her to a life of hard labor and eternal slavery.</string>
<string name="110026">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Deekin. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Ixthyria the Scalesinger.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to resist the temptations of your nemesis Mephistopheles when you faced each other amidst the ruins of Waterdeep.</string>
<string name="110027">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Deekin. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Ixthyria the Scalesinger.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to believe in himself and his capabilities as a worthy adventurer in his own right.</string>
<string name="110028">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Deekin. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Ixthyria the Scalesinger.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to surrender his soul to you that you might be better able to face your nemesis, Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110029">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Deekin. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Ixthyria the Scalesinger.

You recently sold his name to Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss, condemning him to a life of hard labor and eternal slavery.</string>
<string name="110030">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Gargelflaw the Vile.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced Gru&apos;ul to set aside his evil ways and embrace the cause of good.</string>
<string name="110031">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Gargelflaw the Vile.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced Gru&apos;ul to show you the Quarry store that he has kept hidden from you for so long.</string>
<string name="110032">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Gargelflaw the Vile.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced Gru&apos;ul to declare a holiday in your name.</string>
<string name="110033">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss in the City of Lost Souls. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Gargelflaw the Vile.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced Gru&apos;ul to give you a powerful artifact at no cost to yourself or your henchmen.</string>
<string name="110034">Gru&apos;ul the Quarry Boss, also known as Gargelflaw the Vile, is dead. You payed dearly for his True Name but it will be of no further use to you.</string>
<string name="110035">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of her sister, the Knower of Places. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Cordemylia the Knower.

You recently return to her domain, however, only to find it empty. It appears she has already found a safer place in which to hide.</string>
<string name="110036">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have commanded her to reveal the True Name of your nemesis, the arch-devil Mephistopheles. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Thra&apos;axfyl the Ambitious.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently stopped his plans for Lordship over your homeworld of Toril which he hoped would become the Tenth Hell of Baator.</string>
<string name="110037">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have commanded her to reveal the True Name of your nemesis, the arch-devil Mephistopheles. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Thra&apos;axfyl the Ambitious.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced him to let you join in his plans for Lordship over your homeworld of Toril and all the Hells of Baator.</string>
<string name="110038">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have commanded her to reveal the True Name of your nemesis, the arch-devil Mephistopheles. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Thra&apos;axfyl the Ambitious.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently replaced him in his efforts to become Lord of your homeworld, Toril, all the Hells of Baator.</string>
<string name="110039">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have commanded her to reveal the True Name of your nemesis, the arch-devil Mephistopheles. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Thra&apos;axfyl the Ambitious.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently challenged him to a battle that will decide the fate of your homeworld of Toril as well as the various Hells of Baator.</string>
<string name="110040">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Nathyrra. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Qeyifalia the Skyseeker.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to resist the temptations of your nemesis Mephistopheles when you faced each other amidst the ruins of Waterdeep.</string>
<string name="110041">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Nathyrra. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Qeyifalia the Skyseeker.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to forgive herself and finally put the horrors of her past behind her.</string>
<string name="110042">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Nathyrra. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Qeyifalia the Skyseeker.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to surrender her soul to you that you might be better able to face your nemesis, Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110043">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Nathyrra. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Qeyifalia the Skyseeker.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded her to love you despite your various flaws of character.</string>
<string name="110044">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Nathyrra. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Qeyifalia the Skyseeker.

You recently sold her name to Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss, condemning her to a life of hard labor and eternal slavery.</string>
<string name="110045">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sensei Dharvana, leader of the Githzerai Pilgrims trapped in the City of Lost Souls. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Fa&apos;arethia the Misguided.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced her to wake her precious Sleeping Man.</string>
<string name="110046">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sensei Dharvana, leader of the Githzerai Pilgrims trapped in the City of Lost Souls. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Fa&apos;arethia the Misguided.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced her to wake her precious Sleeping Man and admit to the fact that she is his one true love.</string>
<string name="110047">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sensei Dharvana, leader of the Githzerai Pilgrims trapped in the City of Lost Souls. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Fa&apos;arethia the Misguided.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced her to reconcile with the tiefling jester, Arden Swift.</string>
<string name="110048">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sensei Dharvana, leader of the Githzerai Pilgrims trapped in the City of Lost Souls. She is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Fa&apos;arethia the Misguided.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently forced her to abandon her faith in the Sleeping Man.</string>
<string name="110049">Dharvana, the Sensei of the Githzerai Pilgrim, has died. Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you knew her True Name to be Fa&apos;arethia the Misguided. Unfortunately, the value of that knowledge has died with her.</string>
<string name="110050">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sleeping Man. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient.

Empowered by that Knowledge, you recently woke him from his lengthy slumber.</string>
<string name="110051">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sleeping Man. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient.

Empowered by that Knowledge, you recently forced him to leave the City of Lost Souls where he was to meet his one true love.</string>
<string name="110052">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sleeping Man. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient.

Empowered by that Knowledge, you recently forced him to abandon his quest to find his one true love.</string>
<string name="110053">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sleeping Man. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient.

Empowered by that Knowledge, you recently forced him to fight Sensei Dharvana, the Githzerai woman who has fashioned an entire religion around the interpretation of his dreams.</string>
<string name="110054">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Sleeping Man. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient.

Empowered by that Knowledge, you recently commanded him to believe your lies about the identity of his one true love.</string>
<string name="110055">After lying so many years undisturbed, the Sleeping Man lies dead. Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you knew his True Name to be Celesfa&apos;ar the Patient. With his death, however, such knowledge has become useless.</string>
<string name="110056">After learning the identity of his one true love from the Knower of Names, you have returned to the green-skinned Sleeping Man in the City of Lost Souls and informed him of her name.</string>
<string name="110057">After learning that the Sensei Dharvana is the one true love of the Sleeping Man she worships, you have returned to her temple and broken the news. Her reaction was mixed and, in the end, it seems she was more comfortable worshiping the Sleeping Man than being loved by him.</string>
<string name="110058">After learning the identity of his one true love from the Knower of Names, you have returned to the green-skinned Sleeping Man in the City of Lost Souls. With devious intent, you have convinced him that it is someone else entirely.</string>
<string name="110059">After learning that the Sensei Dharvana is the one true love of the Sleeping Man she worships, you have returned to her temple to judge her reaction. With devious intent, however, you have convinced her that it is someone else, a falsehood she seems only too eager to believe.</string>
<string name="110060">Sensei Dharvana, the Sleeping Man&apos;s one true love, is dead. Over the course of many years they shared a closeness that few could imagine but, in the end, they never came to fully know each other as the lovers that the gods intended them to be.</string>
<string name="110061">The Sleeping Man is dead and with him died his lifelong quest to find his one true love.</string>
<string name="110062">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Valen. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Oeskathine the Demonwrestler.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to resist the temptations of your nemesis Mephistopheles when you faced each other amidst the ruins of Waterdeep.</string>
<string name="110063">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Valen. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Oeskathine the Demonwrestler.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to surrender his soul to you that you might be better able to face your nemesis, Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110064">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Valen. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Oeskathine the Demonwrestler.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently commanded him to love you despite your various flaws of character.</string>
<string name="110065">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Valen. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Oeskathine the Demonwrestler.

You recently sold his name to Gru&apos;ul, the foul-mouthed Quarry Boss, condemning him to a life of hard labor and eternal slavery.</string>
<string name="110066">Empowered by the knowledge of the identity of your one true love, you have pursued your ever-developing relationship with great ardor. Already you can imagine yourselves living together happily ever after...</string>
<string name="110067">Uncomfortable with the knowledge of the identity of your one true love, you have chosen to sabotage your still-nascent relationship. Somehow you just can&apos;t seem to come to terms with the destiny the gods have foretold for you.</string>
<string name="110068">Uncomfortable with the knowledge of the identity of your one true love, your heart has led you elsewhere. Somehow you just can&apos;t seem to come to terms with the destiny the gods have foretold for you.</string>
<string name="110069">Empowered by the knowledge of your one true love&apos;s True Name, you have taken on a more cavalier attitude of late. Seizing the opportunity such unfettered power presents, you recently commanded your lover to respond passionately to your advances and overlook the cold-hearted void that lurks within you.</string>
<string name="110070">hx_treas_4</string>
<string name="110071">hx_mimic_enemy_wp_rw_rs045</string>
<string name="110072">hx_treas_1</string>
<string name="110073">Pit Fiend&apos;s Bastard Sword</string>
<string name="110074">Horde Cutscene</string>
<string name="110075">hx_treas_6</string>
<string name="110076">To City of Lost Souls</string>
<string name="110077">Henchmen Waypoint</string>
<string name="110078">hx_frostg_rang</string>
<string name="110079">Smith</string>
<string name="110080">hx_patron_f_rs030</string>
<string name="110081">hx_patron_m_rs030</string>
<string name="110082">hx_treas_5</string>
<string name="110083">Cave Exit</string>
<string name="110084">To Quarry Office</string>
<string name="110085">Fallen One</string>
<string name="110086">Ice Quarry</string>
<string name="110087">hx_treas_2</string>
<string name="110088">hx_treas_003</string>
<string name="110089">Hellbreath Tavern</string>
<string name="110090">h2_spiritfema001_dw_rw_rs020</string>
<string name="110091">h2_spiritfemale_dw_rw_rs020</string>
<string name="110092">h2_spiritfema001_dw_rw_rs040</string>
<string name="110093">h2_spiritfemale_dw_rw_rs040</string>
<string name="110094">Quarry Office</string>
<string name="110095">Gatehouse</string>
<string name="110096">The River Styx</string>
<string name="110097">hx_ice_troll2_rw</string>
<string name="110098">hx_winter_wolf_a</string>
<string name="110099">Waterdeep. One of the greatest cities in all of Faerun, it is home to a multitude of peaceful folk from all races and all walks of life.
Beneath Waterdeep, however, lies a different realm.
This is the deep dungeon known as Undermountain, built by the mad wizard Halaster long before the city was even established above.
Here Halaster tests adventurers who trespass therein with the deadliest of traps and the most dangerous of creatures.  All but the luckiest meet their deaths in its dark halls.
Regardless of this presence beneath them, the people of Waterdeep feel safe enough... for while one may enter Undermountain, it is rare that anything actually comes out...
...until now.
For there is another realm that exists beneath even Undermountain. A place of shadows and evil known only as the Underdark.
It is here that the sinister dark elves known as the Drow rule next to other subterranean horrors unknown to most on the surface world above.
And it is the Drow who now lead an army of these creatures into the streets of Waterdeep, besieging the city from below in a campaign of blood and terror.
And in their darkest hour, the Lords of Waterdeep have issued a call for a hero, someone who can face these dark elves and all of their brethren in their own land, someone who can defeat...
...  the hordes of the Underdark.</string>
<string name="110100">Rogues, or other characters with high dexterity, should take the Weapon Finesse feat and use light weapons, such as short swords and daggers. They are not well suited to using strength based attacks.</string>
<string name="110101">The pit descends into darkness. You cannot tell how deep it is.</string>
<string name="110102"></string>
<string name="110103">&quot;You would question it, &lt;FirstName&gt;?&quot;</string>
<string name="110104">&quot;The truth is what you make of it, &lt;FirstName&gt;. Don&apos;t get too excited yet.&quot;</string>
<string name="110105">&quot;As yours to mine, my love.&quot;</string>
<string name="110106">&quot;Slow down with the poetry, big boy...&quot;</string>
<string name="110107">&quot;&lt;FirstName&gt;?&quot;</string>
<string name="110108">&quot;See how he twists and squirms? You have skewered him well and good, Knower.&quot;</string>
<string name="110109">&quot;You would question it, &lt;FirstName&gt;?&quot;</string>
<string name="110110">&quot;Thank you, Knower. Her name is music to my ears.&quot;</string>
<string name="110111">&quot;Yes, thank you, Knower.&quot;</string>
<string name="110112">&quot;Why? Because my skin is too dark for your love!?&quot;</string>
<string name="110113">&quot;Thank you, Knower. Her name is music to my ears.&quot;</string>
<string name="110114">&quot;The Knower knows of what she speaks...&quot;</string>
<string name="110115">&quot;As yours is to mine, my dear.&quot;</string>
<string name="110116">&quot;Why!? Why can&apos;t it be, &lt;FirstName&gt;?&quot;</string>
<string name="110117">&quot;Thank you, Knower. His name is music to my ears.&quot;</string>
<string name="110118">Remember that you can not sell items while you are shapeshifted. You need to return to your character&apos;s normal form in order to interact with stores.</string>
<string name="110119">You must rest before continuing your adventures.</string>
<string name="110120">You are permanently dead. You must load a savegame.</string>
<string name="110121"></string>
<string name="110122">Invisible Object (Large)</string>
<string name="110123">Use the controls on this page to pick your Editing Language.
Use the Default Language unless you do any of the following:

1) You need to edit a module in a language other than the language used by your game installation. For example, you have the French version of the game, but need to edit a module for German players.

2) You are a translator who is adding translated text to a module. For example, you are editing a module that was created by an English user, and you are adding translated versions of all the text so that Italian users can play the module.

Localized text fields in the toolset have a &quot;...&quot; button next to them to let you edit strings for them in multiple languages.

If you do not use the &quot;...&quot; button and type directly in a localized text field, it will store your text in your chosen Editing Language.

If a localized text string contains text for more than one language, you will see it displayed in your Editing Language whenever possible. Otherwise, it will use the text for the next available language.</string>
<string name="110124">You have acquired an amulet.</string>
<string name="110125">The familiar, hooded figure of the Reaper bows as you approach, enigmatic as always. Distant flames flicker within his reflective, featureless face and you shiver in spite of yourself.</string>
<string name="110126">&quot;How may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110127">&quot;I am sorry, Sojourner,&quot; the Reaper sighs heavily. &quot;You are now barred from the world of Toril. If you are to ask me to return you there, I cannot comply.&quot;</string>
<string name="110128">&quot;I am sorry, Sojourner,&quot; the Reaper sighs heavily. &quot;You are now barred from the world of Toril. I cannot comply.&quot;</string>
<string name="110129">&quot;You are barred from returning to that world by the command of Mephistopheles.&quot; He bows low once again. &quot;I am sorry, Sojourner. It is Mephistopheles who rules here, and so can he command me.&quot;</string>
<string name="110130">&quot;The archdevil uses me as he uses all things, such is his nature. I was not always his subject... but once he learned of my True Name I was his forever.&quot;</string>
<string name="110131">&quot;Not because I desired to. As I said, the archdevil commanded me with the power of my True Name.&quot;</string>
<string name="110132">&quot;Nor does he need to be. As I said, the archdevil commanded me with my True Name... I cannot choose to disobey, even if he is no longer present.&quot;</string>
<string name="110133">&quot;All beings have a True Name that is the definition of their personal essence, their very existence. Should another learn your True Name and speak it to you, they then rule all that you are.&quot;</string>
<string name="110134">&quot;Mephistopheles discovered my True Name long ago, though I know not how. Only he knows it, so he alone commands me despite whatever I might wish.&quot;</string>
<string name="110135">&quot;Mephistopheles used you, as well, creating a devil&apos;s deal that you were unaware of. A bond was formed with him the moment you discovered his relic, and upon killing the one who held him captive you took his place and he yours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110136">&quot;Through your bond, you have assumed the chains that once held Mephistopheles. So as he was once bound to the realm of Cania, so now are you. His prison has become yours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110137">&quot;He traded your freedom for his chains. Once he was bound to the planar realm of Cania but, through his trickery and deceit, he has escaped through the bond he formed with you. So are you now bound to Cania as he once was.&quot;</string>
<string name="110138">&quot;Cania is the Eighth Hell of Baator, the Frozen Wastes and the Dreaded Depths. Here Mephistopheles is Lord of all and prisoner both... or he was, until he slipped his chains and placed them unto you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110139">&quot;You forget, Sojourner... this realm is all places as well as none. We exist in Cania just as everywhere else, part of your prison just as not.&quot;</string>
<string name="110140">He gestures to the mist-shrouded door that stands alone at the far end of the chamber. &quot;That path leads to Cania as it always has, as it has been a part of you since the bond was created. It is no longer barred to your passing.&quot;</string>
<string name="110141">&quot;Alas, I cannot. I have been commanded by Mephistopheles not to allow you to return to Toril, and you no longer possess his relic.&quot;</string>
<string name="110142">&quot;If you learned my True Name you could command me to break the bond between you and return you to Toril. I know not how you would learn of it, however, and I cannot tell it to you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110143">The Reaper nods solemnly. &quot;How may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110144">&quot;I wish you well, Sojourner. Would that I could do more to aid you on your path.&quot;</string>
<string name="110145">The Reaper pauses for a moment, gazing out into the distance as if searching before finally responding. &quot;They are dead, Sojourner. That is, however, merely a transitory state as you are well aware.&quot;</string>
<string name="110146">&quot;The Spirits of the Dead can end up in many places, as their will dictates. The outer planes are infinite in their variety and who can say where a soul will go?&quot;</string>
<string name="110147">&quot;That said, this realm touches all places and so can these dead companions be found. But they will agree to come or not, each according to their desire. I cannot compel them to come here in the same way I have you. Who shall I summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110148">&quot;The spirit refuses... I sense anger and hatred directed at you, Sojourner. He feels wronged by you and will not answer my summons. Is there anyone else you wish me to summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110149">&quot;Consent is given. His spirit travels the gates now, hurtling towards us, and flesh is now forming... your companion returns to you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110150">Valen suddenly appears, as whole as the last time you saw him. He looks around, mildly bewildered. &quot;So I am summoned from beyond the veil once again. To stand at your side, &lt;FirstName&gt;? I am glad to be here with you, then.&quot;</string>
<string name="110151">&quot;When Mephistopheles killed me along with so many of the rebels I thought my time was done.&quot; He turns and regards the Gatekeeper. &quot;And you, strange one... it was you I felt calling me, yes? You&apos;re the one who brought me to this... place?&quot;</string>
<string name="110152">&quot;Yes, fiendish one. &lt;FullName&gt; has requested your presence here in the hells... Now, Sojourner, is there anyone else you wish me to summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110153">&quot;The spirit refuses... I sense anger and hatred directed at you, Sojourner. She feels wronged by you and will not answer my summons. Is there anyone else you wish me to summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110154">&quot;Consent is given. Her spirit travels the gates now, hurtling towards us, and flesh is now forming... your companion returns to you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110155">Nathyrra suddenly appears, looking startled. She draws one of her daggers almost without thinking. &quot;What... where am I?&quot; Her eyes focus on you. &quot;&lt;FirstName&gt;? So I am... alive once more.&quot;</string>
<string name="110156">Slowly she nods, comprehension coming to her. &quot;Thank you for bringing me back, then, my friend. To have died at Mephistopheles&apos;s hand along with so many others was unsettling, to say the least.&quot; She looks around. &quot;And what is this place? Are we in the planes?&quot;</string>
<string name="110157">&quot;Yes, dark one. &lt;FullName&gt; has requested your presence here in the hells... Now, Sojourner, is there anyone else you wish me to summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110158">&quot;Consent is given. His spirit travels the gates now, hurtling towards us, and flesh is now forming... your companion returns to you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110159">Deekin suddenly appears. Strangely, he does not seem surprised nor disturbed by his situation. &quot;There you is, boss! Deekin keeps telling angels that he gots lots to do, that he not stayings up there, but they not believes him!&quot;</string>
<string name="110160">&lt;StartAction&gt;(sigh)&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;Deekin be right all along, just like Deekin says. Stupid angels.&quot; He looks around a bit, taking in the chamber. &quot;Ummm... is we in hell, boss? Place needs good cleaning, maybe.&quot;</string>
<string name="110161">&quot;Yes, little one. &lt;FullName&gt; has requested your presence here in the hells... Now, Sojourner, is there anyone else you wish me to summon?&quot;</string>
<string name="110162">The Reaper nods slowly. &quot;The Sleeping Man is wise and old. He passed through the Gates of Cania when they were first formed, long before the time of my creation.&quot;</string>
<string name="110163">&quot;It has been many ages since I saw him last, yet I suspect he remains there even still, asleep and waiting. Is this so?&quot;</string>
<string name="110164">&quot;Carved about the dais where he sleeps were once the words &apos;She will find you by the Gates of Cania.&apos; And thus he waits for her.&quot;</string>
<string name="110165">&quot;Death or a maiden fair, who can say? The words are there, in answer to a question he must have once asked. That is all I know.&quot;</string>
<string name="110166">&quot;You have learned my True Name, I see... Very well, I have summoned a door that will return you to the one you know as Durnan, in Waterdeep. But, before you go, is there anything else you would have me do?&quot;</string>
<string name="110167">&quot;A word of warning before you go, Sojourner... By breaking the chains Mephistopheles placed upon you and stepping through that door, you forfeit the bond that brought you to this place.&quot;</string>
<string name="110168">&quot;You will not see me again nor lay your eyes upon the ice of Cania.&quot; The Reaper bows deeply. &quot;It has been a... pleasure to serve you. I wish you well, Sojourner.&quot;</string>
<string name="110169">&quot;Consider the Devils of Cania unleashed, m&apos;&lt;Lord/Lady&gt;, but once set loose upon the mortal realm, they will not be easy to rein back in. Even so, I shall comply. Anything more?&quot;</string>
<string name="110170">&quot;If that is your wish, I shall make it so. Even death itself will no longer hold the spirits here. Is there anything else you would ask of me?&quot;</string>
<string name="110171">&quot;As you command, Sojourner. I will return them safely to their home in Limbo. Is there anything else?&quot;</string>
<string name="110172">&quot;Your destination lies here in Cania, thus may I comply... Behold, a Gate has been opened unto you, leading to the place where you last died.&quot;</string>
<string name="110173">&quot;Only what I have already spoken to you. Cania is the Eighth Hell of Baator, a frigid land where Mephistopheles once ruled. It is a plane of torment and evil... be wary should you step unto its icy shores.&quot;</string>
<string name="110174">&quot;There was a time when I roamed free, and I knew much of the Cania that was. I know little of the frozen waste that exists now, however, and I have no power there. I cannot help you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110175">&quot;Remember that you are now bound to Cania. If you knew my True Name, I could break that bond and send you from here. Otherwise even if you were to find another portal I would only retrieve you once more.&quot;</string>
<string name="110176">&quot;I cannot openly betray the one who holds my True Name, Sojourner.&quot; There is almost the hint of a smile in the Reaper&apos;s featureless mirror of a face.</string>
<string name="110177">&quot;Abuse it more than the archdevil himself already has?&quot; The Reaper shakes his head slowly. &quot;I think not.&quot;</string>
<string name="110178">&quot;This I do not know. I cannot provide it to you willingly, Sojourner... and I have no knowledge of how Mephistopheles discovered it. If you did learn it, however, then would you be free.&quot;</string>
<string name="110179">He shakes his head. &quot;I know of none. If any exist, they are well beyond your reach. It would be far easier for you to seek my True Name... though even that is a near impossible task.&quot;</string>
<string name="110180">&quot;You have great power, Sojourner, but I am a part of this realm that is everywhere and nowhere. You could only destroy me if you possessed the power to destroy me in all places... which you do not.&quot;</string>
<string name="110181">&quot;How may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110182">The familiar, hooded figure of the Reaper bows as you approach, enigmatic as always. Distant flames flicker within his reflective, featureless face and you shiver in spite of yourself.</string>
<string name="110183">&quot;How may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110184">You have not visited this realm often since acquiring the Relic of the Reaper, but whenever you have it is always the same... the dire chill in the air seeps through to your bones, and the hum of ancient magic is all around you.</string>
<string name="110185">The familiar, hooded figure of the Reaper bows as you approach, enigmatic as always. Distant flames flicker within his reflective, featureless face and you shiver in spite of yourself.</string>
<string name="110186">The Reaper nods solemnly. &quot;How may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110187">&quot;Much time has passed since last you walked within this hall, Sojourner. Perhaps this is indeed the moment to remind you of the nature of the relic you carry.&quot;</string>
<string name="110188">The Reaper gestures to the small artifact. &quot;The relic is bound to you, and you to it. It is your key to this nexus realm, and you may use it to come here willingly... or be brought here at the moment prior to your death.&quot;</string>
<string name="110189">&quot;This is a nexus realm, Sojourner, a place that touches everywhere and yet nowhere.&quot;</string>
<string name="110190">&quot;If you were brought here to avoid your mortal death, the energy used by the rogue stone will allow me to mark that place and return you there if you wish. You need only ask.&quot;</string>
<string name="110191">The Reaper gestures to the doors behind him. &quot;The central portal is always anchored to your realm, though it may not bring you where you wish to go. The other portals must be anchored to be used.&quot;</string>
<string name="110192">&quot;The gems contain a power that, when consumed, can be felt even from the furthest planes. Think of it as a point of reference, Sojourner, that allows this plane to touch yours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110193">&quot;If you are on your home plane and you possess a rogue stone, you may use its energy to anchor one of this plane&apos;s portals to that spot. After that point, you may use that door to return to that spot at will.&quot;</string>
<string name="110194">&quot;That is a forbidden portal for you, Sojourner, for you yet have life within you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110195">&quot;It is not yet time for you. Use the other portals here and be thankful.&quot;</string>
<string name="110196">&quot;The location moves, from time to time. Always it is tied to somewhere you have been, Sojourner, as this realm is tied to you through the relic.&quot;</string>
<string name="110197">&quot;Nay, Sojourner. In order for the relic to transport you here so quickly so as to avoid your death, it requires great energy... energy it can only draw from a rogue stone.&quot;</string>
<string name="110198">&quot;So long as you carry such a stone in your possession you are indeed safe. Should you not have one, however, you will perish... as all mortals do.&quot;</string>
<string name="110199">&quot;As you wish. How else may I serve you, Sojourner?&quot;</string>
<string name="110200">&quot;As you wish, Sojourner. Should you have need of me, here I shall remain.&quot;</string>
<string name="110201">&quot;Behold, Sojourner... A Gate has been opened unto you that you might join with the leader of your fellows.&quot;</string>
<string name="110202">&quot;Behold, Sojourner... A Gate has been opened unto you, leading to the place where you last died.&quot;</string>
<string name="110203">&quot;I am bound to it, Sojourner, as it is bound to you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110204">&quot;It is, however, the only answer that I can give.&quot; The Reaper bows low, sounding almost apologetic. &quot;The relic is what it is, just as you are. Better to ask who created you, Sojourner.&quot;</string>
<string name="110205">&quot;This is the Gatehouse, an entry point into the Land of the Dead,&quot; he gestures all about him. &quot;You are welcome here but I do not recommend you linger.&quot;</string>
<string name="110206">&quot;I know of none, for it is not my place to know such things. I am part of this realm, and it is all of my concern.&quot;</string>
<string name="110207">&quot;That is not for you, Sojourner,&quot; he interrupts. &quot;Seek it not, for it is not yet your time to pass through it.&quot;</string>
<string name="110208">&quot;As I have already spoken, it is not yet your time. I can say no more.&quot;</string>
<string name="110209">&quot;Have you forgotten already, Sojourner? If you wish, I can speak of the relic you carry and its relation to the nexus realm.&quot;</string>
<string name="110210">&quot;Than what else would you ask of this realm?&quot;</string>
<string name="110211">&quot;As I have already reminded you, they are points that may be anchored to your plane. Until then, they drift free and lead nowhere but here.&quot;</string>
<string name="110212">&quot;It is nowhere, and yet everywhere. This is a nexus realm, Sojourner, that is tied to you... it touches on all places that you were, are and will be.&quot;</string>
<string name="110213">&quot;Understanding is not required. The only requirement is that you carry the relic with you. Therefore the nexus is yours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110214">&quot;You have asked me this many times, Sojourner, and yet I give you the only answer I can: I am the Reaper, the Gatherer of Dust, the Gatekeeper... and this is my realm.&quot;</string>
<string name="110215">&quot;I rule this place only so far as any being can rule themselves. We are the same, this realm and I. I am King but never master.&quot;</string>
<string name="110216">The Reaper&apos;s reflective face reveals no emotion, yet he pauses. &quot;You hold the Relic of the Reaper, Sojourner. Therefore you rule here... for now.&quot;</string>
<string name="110217">&quot;I am bound to it as it is bound to you. So long as you hold it, you command this place... and therefore you command me.&quot;</string>
<string name="110218">&quot;I cannot leave this place, Sojourner, for I am this place. As I am tied to the relic you carry, so do I already journey with you always.&quot;</string>
<string name="110219">&quot;I am not a slave, nor am I prisoner. A place can be a prison, but cannot itself be imprisoned... though it can be commanded. Remember that.&quot;</string>
<string name="110220">&quot;I have always been here. As this nexus realm was created, so was I created with it. We are the same, one an extension of the other.&quot;</string>
<string name="110221">&quot;I could give you the answer to your question, Sojourner, but it would mean nothing to you. Those who created us are passed out of knowing.&quot;</string>
<string name="110222">&quot;I am a being of the planes, Sojourner... no more, no less.&quot; You think there is almost a hint of a smile in the Reaper&apos;s blank features.</string>
<string name="110223">&quot;Surely. And yet not a one of them is my True Name.&quot;</string>
<string name="110224">&quot;All beings have a True Name, Sojourner. Even you. It defines the essence of your being and gives you power over your actions. Always it must remain secret.&quot;</string>
<string name="110225">&quot;To surrender your True Name is to surrender your power, your very essence, to another. Be glad that as a mortal you are unaware of it and thus may never surrender it.&quot;</string>
<string name="110226">&quot;You have not truly perished,&quot; the figure reminds you, &quot;as the relic will always pull you to this realm at the very moment of your death. From here,&quot; he gestures to the doors behind him, &quot;you may return to whence you came.&quot;</string>
<string name="110227">The Reaper&apos;s emotionless face gleams at you from the darkness. It seems he has nothing left to say to you.</string>
<string name="110228">&quot;I need to ask you something.&quot;</string>
<string name="110229">&quot;I have died and wish to return to where I fell.&quot;</string>
<string name="110230">&quot;But Toril is my home!&quot;</string>
<string name="110231">&quot;You can&apos;t comply? But I command you!&quot;</string>
<string name="110232">&quot;What? Who says I&apos;m barred from there?&quot;</string>
<string name="110233">&quot;So you worked for Mephistopheles all along.&quot;</string>
<string name="110234">&quot;I knew it! You lied to me!&quot;</string>
<string name="110235">&quot;His forever? What do you mean?&quot;</string>
<string name="110236">&quot;But he&apos;s not here to command you now.&quot;</string>
<string name="110237">&quot;What is a True Name?&quot;</string>
<string name="110238">&quot;So am I stuck here forever?&quot;</string>
<string name="110239">&quot;What do you mean he took my place?&quot;</string>
<string name="110240">&quot;Cania? Isn&apos;t that one of the Nine Hells?&quot;</string>
<string name="110241">&quot;The realm of Cania? What do you mean?&quot;</string>
<string name="110242">&quot;Here? But... I&apos;m not in Cania, am I?&quot;</string>
<string name="110243">&quot;Is there nothing you can do to help me?&quot;</string>
<string name="110244">&quot;I have other questions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110245">&quot;I must go.&quot;</string>
<string name="110246">&quot;What of my companions? Where are they?&quot;</string>
<string name="110247">&quot;No, summon no one.&quot;</string>
<string name="110248">&quot;Summon forth Valen.&quot;</string>
<string name="110249">&quot;Summon forth Nathyrra.&quot;</string>
<string name="110250">&quot;Summon forth Deekin.&quot;</string>
<string name="110251">&quot;I can&apos;t think of anyone else.&quot;</string>
<string name="110252">&quot;I seek the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man.&quot;</string>
<string name="110253">&quot;Yes, it is. What is he waiting for?&quot;</string>
<string name="110254">&quot;And who is &apos;she&apos;?&quot;</string>
<string name="110255">&quot;So tell me again what I could do to return home?&quot;</string>
<string name="110256">&quot;Hecugoth the Abandoned, I command you to grant me passage home!&quot;</string>
<string name="110257">&quot;Thank you, Reaper. That will be all.&quot;</string>
<string name="110258">&quot;Allow the Devils to wreak their havoc on the planes.&quot;</string>
<string name="110259">&quot;Allow the Spirits of the Dead to haunt the Living.&quot;</string>
<string name="110260">&quot;Allow the Githzerai Pilgrims to return home.&quot;</string>
<string name="110261">&quot;I have died and wish to return to where I fell.&quot;</string>
<string name="110262">&quot;What do you know about Cania?&quot;</string>
<string name="110263">&quot;Surely there are other ways back to Toril?&quot;</string>
<string name="110264">&quot;You sound as if you&apos;d prefer to betray Mephistopheles.&quot;</string>
<string name="110265">&quot;But aren&apos;t you worried that I might abuse your True Name?&quot;</string>
<string name="110266">&quot;How could I discover your True Name?&quot;</string>
<string name="110267">&quot;Are there any other relics?&quot;</string>
<string name="110268">&quot;What is Cania?&quot;</string>
<string name="110269">&quot;I should destroy you for betraying me.&quot;</string>
<string name="110270">&quot;I require your assistance. Quickly.&quot;</string>
<string name="110271">&quot;So we meet again.&quot;</string>
<string name="110272">&quot;It is good to see you again, Reaper.&quot;</string>
<string name="110273">&quot;I would like to know more about how the Relic works.&quot;</string>
<string name="110274">&quot;How do I return home from here?&quot;</string>
<string name="110275">&quot;Why are rogue stones so important?&quot;</string>
<string name="110276">&quot;What do you mean by anchoring?&quot;</string>
<string name="110277">&quot;What about the far door, the one covered in mist?&quot;</string>
<string name="110278">&quot;You have to be dead to go through it?&quot;</string>
<string name="110279">&quot;Where does the central portal go?&quot;</string>
<string name="110280">&quot;So I am immortal? I cannot die?&quot;</string>
<string name="110281">&quot;I&apos;ve heard enough about the Relic.&quot;</string>
<string name="110282">&quot;I must go.&quot;</string>
<string name="110283">&quot;Tell me about the Relic again.&quot;</string>
<string name="110284">&quot;I must go to the leader of my adventuring party.&quot;</string>
<string name="110285">&quot;I have died and wish to return to where I fell.&quot;</string>
<string name="110286">&quot;But who created the relic? What is it?&quot;</string>
<string name="110287">&quot;That&apos;s not an answer.&quot;</string>
<string name="110288">&quot;Tell me about your realm once again.&quot;</string>
<string name="110289">&quot;Are there many places like this?&quot;</string>
<string name="110290">&quot;There is a door at the far end of the room, covered in mist...&quot;</string>
<string name="110291">&quot;Why not?&quot;</string>
<string name="110292">&quot;What are all these doors?&quot;</string>
<string name="110293">&quot;No, not yet.&quot;</string>
<string name="110294">&quot;Yes, do that.&quot;</string>
<string name="110295">&quot;But...where is this place exactly?&quot;</string>
<string name="110296">&quot;I don&apos;t understand.&quot;</string>
<string name="110297">&quot;I would like to know more about you.&quot;</string>
<string name="110298">&quot;Enough of that, then.&quot;</string>
<string name="110299">&quot;Do you rule here? Or do you serve another?&quot;</string>
<string name="110300">&quot;Is that an answer?&quot;</string>
<string name="110301">&quot;What is the significance of the relic?&quot;</string>
<string name="110302">&quot;So could I command you to come with me?&quot;</string>
<string name="110303">&quot;Is there no way to free you?&quot;</string>
<string name="110304">&quot;How did you come to be here?&quot;</string>
<string name="110305">&quot;Who created this realm, then?&quot;</string>
<string name="110306">&quot;But... what *are* you, exactly?&quot;</string>
<string name="110307">&quot;That is a lot of names.&quot;</string>
<string name="110308">&quot;True Name?&quot;</string>
<string name="110309">&quot;Why must it be secret?&quot;</string>
<string name="110310">&quot;It seems I died once again.&quot;</string>
<string name="110311">This blade is almost as nasty as the personality that now permanently resides within it. With each hit, it draws a little bit of the life-force inside and uses some of it to heal the wielder. Whether it could potentially draw more of that life-force, or has other side effects, is unknown... even to Enserric himself. The long-dead mage has been within the weapon for quite a while but has not gotten much use, seeing as for decades the primary user was even deader than Enserric. ...hmmm. Deader? More dead? Can something be more dead? This is exactly the sort of question that makes Enserric clam up and begin muttering in pure agitation...</string>
<string name="110312">&quot;I guess I could answer a few questions for you. Can&apos;t see any harm in it. Besides, it&apos;s not like the Maker&apos;s golems here on the island will tell you anything.&quot; She smiles briefly at her own joke.</string>
<string name="110313">&quot;Well, the island was named after the ancient duergar mage who built his stronghold here centuries ago. They say the Maker came here so he could work in peace while perfecting his golems.&quot;</string>
<string name="110314">&quot;There must be some truth to these stories. There&apos;s some ruins to the north that could have been the Maker&apos;s laboratory, though all that&apos;s left is the dungeon. And there&apos;s the golems, of course.&quot;</string>
<string name="110315">&quot;The dungeon at the north end of the island is crawling with golems. At least, the first floor of it is. We don&apos;t go any deeper. We figure they&apos;re guardians left over from the Maker. &quot;</string>
<string name="110316">&quot;They must have been built to protect against thieves and scavengers.&quot; She gives you a rueful look. &quot;They do a pretty good job, too. We&apos;ve lost more than a few duergar during our expeditions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110317">She shakes her head. &quot;Not possible. There&apos;s some kind of scavenger golem in there that repairs and rebuilds any golems we manage to take down.&quot;  </string>
<string name="110318">&quot;We&apos;ve tried to kill the scavenger, but it&apos;s got a number of magical defenses. Every time we attack it, it teleports away to safety. That damn thing makes our job a lot tougher.&quot;</string>
<string name="110319">&quot;Everything I know about the Maker comes from legends and myths. They say he was a powerful duergar sorcerer who isolated himself on this island to work on his research.&quot;</string>
<string name="110320">&quot;His specialty was crafting golems. According to the legends, he found a way to imbue his constructs with intelligence and free will. But the golems we&apos;ve run into seem pretty standard to me.&quot; </string>
<string name="110321">&quot;Nobody really knows; he disappeared five centuries ago. Most people think he was killed off by his own creations: intelligent golems with a will of their own.&quot;</string>
<string name="110322">&quot;I don&apos;t know if I really believe that, but it makes a good story. The only golems we&apos;ve run across in the dungeon don&apos;t seem all that smart to me. Damn tough to kill, though.&quot;</string>
<string name="110323">This duergar female looks you up and down, gauging your strength and trying to judge if you are a threat. Satisfied that you pose no immediate harm, she seems to relax slightly.</string>
<string name="110324">The duergar raise their weapons, but at a signal from their leader they hold their ground. She gives you a quick once over, evaluating you as a potential threat.</string>
<string name="110325">&quot;If this is a joke, you picked the wrong group to play games with. We&apos;re not looking for a fight, but we&apos;re well armed and we will defend ourselves.&quot;</string>
<string name="110326">&quot;You should&apos;ve picked an easier target! Attack!&quot;</string>
<string name="110327">She nods. &quot;Fair enough. As long as you aren&apos;t here to cause trouble for us, you can keep your secrets. My name is Dahanna. I&apos;m the leader of this expedition.&quot;</string>
<string name="110328">The duergar visibly relaxes, though she is still studying you carefully as she addresses you once more. &quot;My name is Dahanna. I&apos;m the leader of this expedition.&quot;</string>
<string name="110329">&quot;Come and go as you please, surfacer. You don&apos;t answer to us.&quot;</string>
<string name="110330">She nods thoughtfully. &quot;The Valsharess. I&apos;ve heard about her. One of the drow matron mothers, isn&apos;t she? She&apos;s made quite a name for herself recently.&quot;</string>
<string name="110331">&quot;I hear she&apos;s been attacking the surface... I guess that&apos;s why you&apos;re looking to stop her. But you won&apos;t find any help against her here. If the drow don&apos;t bother us, we don&apos;t bother them.&quot;</string>
<string name="110332">&lt;StartCheck&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna shakes her head slowly. &quot;I don&apos;t want trouble with you, surfacer. But you bullying us won&apos;t make us join you. Our minds are set; you can&apos;t change them.&quot;</string>
<string name="110333">&lt;StartCheck&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna shrugs. &quot;Maybe. But the Valsharess isn&apos;t the first drow we&apos;ve seen rise to power. Most of them get toppled long before they ever turn their attention to us.&quot;</string>
<string name="110334">&quot;We&apos;re treasure hunters. Centuries ago, this island was home to a powerful duergar wizard known as the Maker, or so the stories go. The Maker&apos;s long gone, but he left a few things behind.&quot; </string>
<string name="110335">&quot;We come out here to salvage rare metal and pieces of golems from the ruins of the Maker&apos;s tower. You&apos;d be surprised what the right buyer will pay for an arm made of pure adamantine.&quot;</string>
<string name="110336">She grins. &quot;But it isn&apos;t easy. Not too many expeditions come here anymore. There&apos;s still some good metal to be found, but you have to be willing to go toe-to-toe with the Maker&apos;s golems.&quot;</string>
<string name="110337">&quot;As usual, the duergar are scavengers, living off the scraps of others.&quot;</string>
<string name="110338">&quot;Better watch your tongue, drow! This is duergar territory. Your arrogance might have cost you more than you&apos;re willing to pay.&quot;</string>
<string name="110339">Dahanna and the other duergar approach you. You notice their weapons are drawn and that they have packed up their camp. Dahanna appears uncomfortable, as if she is ashamed of what is about to happen. </string>
<string name="110340">&lt;StartAction&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna smiles. &quot;You&apos;re &lt;race&gt; lies don&apos;t fool me. You were in there far too long to come out empty handed. Now, give us what&apos;s rightfully ours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110341">&lt;StartAction&gt;Success&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna cocks her head to the side, considering your words. &quot;You seem sincere. I can&apos;t say for sure whether you&apos;re lying or not,&quot; she finally admits. </string>
<string name="110342">There&apos;s some angry grumbling from the other soldiers, but she cuts them off with a sharp gesture. &quot;I&apos;m not going to let this come to bloodshed only to find out we were fighting over nothing.&quot;</string>
<string name="110343">&lt;StartAction&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;We&apos;ve held our own against the Maker&apos;s golems. I think we can manage against a &lt;race&gt; surfacer like you. We&apos;ll fight for what is rightfully ours.&quot;</string>
<string name="110344">&lt;StartAction&gt;Success&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna studies you closely, then seems to come to a decision. &quot;You&apos;re probably right, surfacer. We&apos;re not willing to throw our lives away.&quot;</string>
<string name="110345">&quot;You&apos;ve gone deeper into the Maker&apos;s dungeon than we ever did, and you&apos;ve come back to tell the tale. We&apos;d be foolish to go up against you, even as desperate as we are.&quot;</string>
<string name="110346">&lt;StartAction&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;We&apos;ve been working this island for twenty years, and we&apos;ve lost our fair share of duergar. We&apos;ve paid our dues... you owe us something!&quot;</string>
<string name="110347">&lt;StartAction&gt;Success&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;Maybe... maybe you&apos;re right, surfacer. We aren&apos;t thieves, we earn our living honestly.&quot; There is some angry grumbling from the soldiers, but Dahanna cuts them off with a single gesture.</string>
<string name="110348">The leader of the duergar shakes her head. &quot;I&apos;m sorry for this. But  we count on these expeditions to survive. Each time we come back, we find less and less good metal. We are growing desperate.&quot;</string>
<string name="110349">Dahanna looks at you with obvious disbelief, though she takes the offered coins. &quot;You would do this for us, after what just happened? You are more forgiving than we duergar, surfacer.&quot;</string>
<string name="110350">She smiles. &quot;Thank you for this gift. Our expedition here is over now, we&apos;re heading back to our homes and our families. It will be nice to return with a few extra coins.&quot;</string>
<string name="110351">&quot;Our expedition here is over now, surfacer. We&apos;re heading back to our homes and our families.&quot;</string>
<string name="110352">&quot;I can&apos;t honestly say whether we will come back to this island again. In any case, we wish you luck, surfacer. Remember: the Underdark is a dangerous place.&quot;</string>
<string name="110353">She nods. &quot;Maybe you&apos;re right. Perhaps the rewards here are no longer worth the risks. There are other places we can go, places far less dangerous than this island.&quot;</string>
<string name="110354">&lt;StartAction&gt;Failure&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna considers your counter offer carefully, calculating the chances of her group against you. Finally she shakes her head.</string>
<string name="110355">&quot;One thousand gold won&apos;t go very far, split between all of us. I think we&apos;ve earned the right to at least 10,000, considering you&apos;re poaching our claim here.&quot;</string>
<string name="110356">Dahanna sighs. &quot;I was hoping it wouldn&apos;t come to this, but I can see you aren&apos;t being reasonable. Attack!&quot;</string>
<string name="110357">&lt;StartAction&gt;Success&lt;/Start&gt; Dahanna considers your counter offer carefully, calculating the chances of her group against you. Finally, she nods in acceptance. </string>
<string name="110358">The soldiers behind Dahanna begin to murmur excitedly, but she cuts them off with a sharp hand gesture. She takes the offered coins and says, &quot;I&apos;m glad this was done without bloodshed.&quot;</string>
<string name="110359">&quot;A polite thief is still a thief. Being courteous doesn&apos;t make this right.&quot;</string>
<string name="110360">&quot;Well, at least you is polite... for a thief.&quot;</string>
<string name="110361">&quot;Well, at least you&apos;re being courteous while you rob us. That&apos;s more than I expected from your kind.&quot;</string>
<string name="110362">Nathyrra spits on the ground. &quot;You would bargain with this hargluk?&quot; </string>
<string name="110363">Dahanna ignores her. &quot;If you give us 10,000 gold pieces, we&apos;ll let you go on your way without any trouble. If not, we&apos;ll take what&apos;s rightfully ours by force.&quot;</string>
<string name="110364">&quot;Nothing personal? That&apos;s funny. When a pack of armed thugs points their weapons at me, I tend to take it *very* personally.&quot;</string>
<string name="110365">&quot;Look, Boss! Them duergar is coming to give us a welcome back surprise party... uh, wait. Deekin not thinks this a party after all. Too bad. Deekin wants cake.&quot;</string>
<string name="110366">&quot;I want to ask you some questions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110367">&quot;Tell me more about the island.&quot;</string>
<string name="110368">&quot;Tell me about the golems.&quot;</string>
<string name="110369">&quot;I would&apos;ve thought you&apos;d cleared all the golems out by now.&quot;</string>
<string name="110370">&quot;Tell me about the Maker.&quot;</string>
<string name="110371">&quot;What happened to him?&quot;</string>
<string name="110372">&quot;Friend or foe? Uh... I guess I&apos;ll pick foe!&quot;</string>
<string name="110373">&quot;It&apos;s no joke. I just want to slaughter you all. I&apos;m funny that way.&quot;</string>
<string name="110374">&quot;Calm down. I&apos;m not looking for a fight, either.&quot;</string>
<string name="110375">&quot;My name and business are my own.&quot;</string>
<string name="110376">&quot;My name is &lt;FullName&gt;. I don&apos;t mean any harm.&quot;</string>
<string name="110377">&quot;I&apos;ll be going now.&quot;</string>
<string name="110378">&quot;Time for this to get bloody. Die, you Underdark excuse for a dwarf!&quot;</string>
<string name="110379">&quot;I&apos;m looking for allies to help me against the Valsharess.&quot;</string>
<string name="110380">&lt;StartCheck&gt;Persuade: Intimidate&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;You&apos;re either with me or against me. Think about it.&quot;</string>
<string name="110381">&quot;I gave you a chance. Now you&apos;ll pay the price!&quot; &lt;StartAction&gt;Attack.&lt;/Start&gt;</string>
<string name="110382">&quot;Fine. I want to ask you something else then.&quot;</string>
<string name="110383">&lt;StartCheck&gt;Persuade&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;Eventually the Valsharess will turn her army against the duergar, too.&quot;</string>
<string name="110384">&quot;What are you doing here?&quot;</string>
<string name="110385">&quot;I have some other questions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110386">&quot;Relax. We&apos;ll just be going now.&quot;</string>
<string name="110387">&quot;Settle down. We just want to ask you some questions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110388">&quot;Nobody threatens me! Death to the duergar!&quot; &lt;StartAction&gt;Attack.&lt;/Start&gt;</string>
<string name="110389">&quot;Is this some kind of shake down?&quot;</string>
<string name="110390">&quot;Your island? What are you talking about?&quot;</string>
<string name="110391">&quot;I think I see where this is going...&quot;</string>
<string name="110392">&quot;Maybe we could work out a deal.&quot;</string>
<string name="110393">&lt;StartAction&gt;Persuade:Bluff&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;I didn&apos;t find anything worthwhile. You&apos;ve picked this place clean.&quot;</string>
<string name="110394">&lt;StartAction&gt;Persuade: Intimidate&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;Careful now. This may be more than you can handle.&quot;</string>
<string name="110395">&lt;StartAction&gt;Persuade&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;You have no right to my stuff. I did all the work!&quot;</string>
<string name="110396">&quot;Apology *not* accepted! You&apos;ll pay for this with blood!&quot;</string>
<string name="110397">&quot;Sounds like times are tough. Here&apos;s a thousand gold to help you out.&quot;</string>
<string name="110398">&quot;That&apos;s okay. There&apos;s no hard feelings.&quot;</string>
<string name="110399">&quot;Maybe it&apos;s time you moved on to somewhere else.&quot;</string>
<string name="110400">&lt;StartAction&gt;Persuade&lt;/Start&gt; &quot;I&apos;ll give you a thousand gold... no more.&quot;</string>
<string name="110401">No deal.</string>
<string name="110402">Here&apos;s the 10,000 gold.</string>
<string name="110403">Staff of Sodalis</string>
<string name="110404">This vile staff was wielded by Sodalis, the fearsome High Priest of Vix&apos;thra who ruled over the free-village of Drearing&apos;s Deep in the Underdark. The swirling vortex at the staff&apos;s tip is said to be a god&apos;s-eye view of the infinite layers of the Abyss.</string>
<string name="110405">Deathslayer</string>
<string name="110406">Rumor has it that Deathslayer was originally crafted for use by an assassin sent to eliminate a powerful lich. His fate is still unknown, but it&apos;s doubtful he would have willingly abandoned this blade.</string>
<string name="110407">Unmaking</string>
<string name="110408">Originally wielded by an unknown gnomish hero who single-handedly wiped out the evil wizard Tnert&apos;s legions of golems, this blade&apos;s whereabouts have become the subject of tavern gossip.</string>
<string name="110409">Female Thrall</string>
<string name="110410">You&apos;ve purchased a female thrall from the illithid and sent her off to the fighting pits - a truly grim fate. At least you&apos;ll be able to wager on her battles... until she dies.</string>
<string name="110411">You&apos;ve purchased a female thrall from the illithid. However, once free from their mind controlling powers she attacked you. Obviously, she would rather die than live her life in servitude.</string>
<string name="110412">You&apos;ve come up with a plan to gain the freedom of the female thrall you purchased from the illithid. Because of the mind flayers&apos; telepathic abilities, you can&apos;t reveal your plan to her.

You&apos;ve sent her to deliver a fake message to the Seer. Since she believes she is magically bound to you, the illithid will consider her a thrall in your service and allow her to leave their city. Once back at the rebel camp, you can explain the truth to her.</string>
<string name="110413">You&apos;ve purchased a female thrall from the illithid and sent her off to the fighting pits - she fought bravely but died as a gladiator.</string>
<string name="110414">The thrall you freed from the illithid managed to find her way back to the Seer&apos;s camp. Once the threat of the Valsharess is no more, the Seer has promised to help her find her way back to the surface so she can leave the Underdark behind her forever.</string>
<string name="110415">The female thrall from the illithid slave market has been killed.</string>
<string name="110416">Thrall Revolt</string>
<string name="110417">You&apos;ve freed a group of thralls from the pens of Zorvak&apos;Mur. Though eager for freedom, you&apos;ve convinced them to wait until you reach the Elder Brain before they begin their revolt. However, you know that if their rebellion succeeds, any chance of convincing the illithid to abandon the Valsharess is likely gone.</string>
<string name="110418">You&apos;ve freed a group of thralls from the pens of Zorvak&apos;Mur. Under their leader, Argosus, they&apos;ve launched a bid for freedom. The only downside is that you&apos;ve likely destroyed any chance you had of convincing the illithid to abandon the Valsharess.</string>
<string name="110419">You&apos;ve betrayed Argosus and his followers in order to garner the goodwill of the Zorvak&apos;Mur Overmind. No doubt the thralls will suffer terribly for their attempted escape, but it&apos;s a price you&apos;re willing to pay.
</string>
<string name="110420">You&apos;ve freed a group of thralls from the pens of Zorvak&apos;Mur, and they plan to start a rebellion once you&apos;ve reached the Elder Brain. Should their revolt succeed, you likely won&apos;t have any chance of gaining the support of Zorvak&apos;Mur or the illithid in your cause.</string>
<string name="110421">You&apos;ve betrayed the thrall rebellion for the sake of the greater good. By denying Argosus and his followers their freedom, you still have a chance to convince the Zorvak&apos;Mur Elder Brain to help you against the Valsharess.</string>
<string name="110422">Sinkhole</string>
<string name="110423">Aghaaz&apos;s Camp</string>
<string name="110424">Ambush Spot</string>
<string name="110425">Sodalis</string>
<string name="110426">Sodalis&apos; Robe</string>
<string name="110427">&quot;...As wise and powerful as you are, Eye Tyrant Arutha, your lack of progress on the matters we have agreed to angers me. You promised me at least a dozen beholders to help attack the rebellious drow. What I have seen from you thus far is only two beholders! I am sending some of my slaves with this letter to escort the remaining beholders. Satisfy me and I may not bind you to spend the rest of eternity in the dark. Exceed my expectations and I will give you their weight in gold as well. Disappoint me, however, and I will destroy even the memory of your pathetic little hive. The choice is yours...&quot;</string>
<string name="110428">Enter</string>
<string name="110429">Gatehouse</string>
<string name="110430">&quot;Pike off. Gru&apos;ul declared a holiday.&quot;</string>
<string name="110431">&quot;Talk all you want, berk. Gru&apos;ul declared a holiday so I&apos;ve got the time.&quot;</string>
<string name="110432">&quot;Honor? Honor!? Honor, my great-aunt Ninny&apos;s soggy bum it&apos;s honor! This here is punishment, berk! If the Big M had wanted to honor me, he wouldn&apos;t have put me in charge of this lot of boot-licking incompetents!&quot;</string>
<string name="110433">&quot;He named you Quarry Boss? That must be quite the honor...&quot;</string>
<string name="110434">&quot;It hurts to use them, I&apos;ll have you know. &apos;Tis a good thing I take pleasure in my own suffering. What aspect of my former self would you have me tap?&quot;</string>
<string name="110435">&quot;Yes, let us play at being good no more...&quot;</string>
<string name="110436">&quot;Of course, &lt;FirstName&gt;.&quot;</string>
<string name="110437">&quot;I want you to use one of your special abilities.&quot;</string>
<string name="110438">&quot;No, that&apos;s it.&quot;</string>
<string name="110439">&quot;Goodbye.&quot;</string>
<string name="110440">&quot;Back to my previous questions.&quot;</string>
<string name="110441">&quot;Time seems different in the cold... Memory... seems different... All I know is that we chose this place, somehow...  Welcome to the Eighth Hell of Baator, I suppose...&quot;</string>
<string name="110442">&quot;No! I will not believe it! You are but a devil sent to tempt me! If you wish me to believe it, you must bring me proof. All else is falsehood!&quot;</string>
<string name="110443">&quot;Did I say yes? I meant no.&quot;</string>
<string name="110444">&quot;I saw her corpse in the other room.&quot;</string>
<string name="110445">&quot;In the passing of seven spokes a hole was dug and a fearsome devil freed. Had the digging been done but sixteen spokes the sooner, it would have uncovered what you need.&quot;</string>
<string name="110446">&quot;I am an ancient baatorian, Planetar. With every answer, I become more like the question.&quot;</string>
<string name="110447">Deekin looks at you with big, soulful eyes. &quot;You... you would miss me, boss? Then... then Deekin not goings to betray you!&quot; He suddenly turns on Mephistopheles. &quot;You may be bigger than the boss, BUT DEEKIN NOT LIKES YOU!!&quot;</string>
<string name="110448">&quot;My love will go where it wishes, devil. All the promises you could make are nothing next to all this woman here can offer me. Consider your offer refused.&quot;</string>
<string name="110449">Valen glares at the archdevil. &quot;It would not be worth betraying my love for &lt;FirstName&gt;, that is sure. If there is a taint to be removed today, it is yours, devil!&quot;</string>
<string name="110450">&quot;But I embrace that killer in you, Nathyrra... Set aside your guilt! Be true to yourself! You are a Red Sister. Join with me, Nathyrra. As a Red Sister, who would you rather serve? &lt;FullName&gt; or myself...?&quot;</string>
<string name="110451">Nathyrra ponders his words for a long moment, then smiles sadly at him. &quot;I would rather serve the one I love. I may still be a killer but let it be you I kill today, Mephistopheles.&quot;</string>
<string name="110452">The battle still rages on the far bank. If you have plans for this catapult, they will have to wait.</string>
<string name="110453">Frost clings to this spirit&apos;s form. Her eyes bear a commanding gaze.</string>
<string name="110454">The tall, grey-skinned woman appears calm before you, her countenance somber. Muscles ripple beneath her leathery skin.</string>
<string name="110455">There is a dark malevolence to your newfound ally and a tension in the air when you&apos;re around her. </string>
<string name="110456">There is a righteous vigor to Aribeth&apos;s ghostly form and her former reticence seems barely a memory.</string>
<string name="110457">Though her impressive wings flutter, the Knower of Places makes no breeze. You wonder if she was born in this form or has somehow chosen it along the way.</string>
<string name="110458">Worn by devout githzerai, these woven strappings are adorned with passages from various religious texts that they hold dear.</string>
<string name="110459">Small Silver Key</string>
<string name="110460">This hastily scrawled note bears Mephistopheles&apos; now-familiar script:

&quot;I am about to make my move and lay claim to Toril. Perhaps the Tanar&apos;ri have caught wind of this for I have just received word that they are launching an assault near where I have stationed you. Stray catapult fire from the battle has already melted through the ice and freed one of my treacherous generals. Make your way to the prison and fend the Tanar&apos;ri off at all costs. The last thing I need is some fool demon getting his paws on my Knower of Names. Serve me well and I may give you lordship over Waterdeep once it is mine...&quot;

It appears that this particular front of the Blood War was opened just before he left for your homeworld, Toril.</string>
<string name="110461">Waterdeep</string>
<string name="110462">Zorvak&apos;Mur</string>
<string name="110463">Cania</string>
<string name="110464">Meph Chain</string>
<string name="110465">Drearing&apos;s Deep</string>
<string name="110466">Followers of Eilistraee</string>
<string name="110467">In speaking with the Spirits of the Dead who cluster around the Gates of Cania, you have learned that they had a leader who had stood up to Mephistopheles when he first announced that he would be devouring their souls to fuel his undead army in your homeworld of Toril. He must have done something dire to her, however, for after the confrontation, she fled to a cave in the center of the city where she now refuses to speak with anyone. The Spirits say she&apos;s becoming one of the Lost, those who have given up hope and are slowly merging with the icy essence of Cania.</string>
<string name="110468">You have rescued Aribeth de Tylmarande, the ghostly leader of the Spirits of the Dead, from the icy grip of Cania. Thanks to your efforts and persistence, she has dedicated what remains of this threadbare afterlife to the cause of evil. With that, you have restored her to her former status as a fearsome Blackguard and she has offered to aid you in your quest through the Hells.</string>
<string name="110469">Trapped here much like you, a group of githzerai Pilgrims have related an interesting tale regarding a certain fellow named Arden Swift who has been traveling with them for the past while. According to the prevailing gossip, Arden got into an argument with the Pilgrims&apos; leader regarding his sacriligious plans to wake the so-called Sleeping Man who the Pilgrims are here to visit. Arden&apos;s currently drowning his sorrows in the Hellbreath Tavern in the city&apos;s southeast corner.</string>
<string name="110470">You have met a jester, Arden Swift, in the Hellbreath Tavern in the city&apos;s southeast corner. He seems somehow associated with the githzerai Pilgrims currently patronizing the establishment but, given his tiefling heritage and the dirty looks they occasionally slip him over their half-empty tankards, you&apos;re unsure how.</string>
<string name="110471">In talking with Arden Swift, a bard traveling with the githzerai, he has told you of his rather sacriligious plans to wake their so-called Sleeping Man using a Trumpet of Pandemonium he acquired somewhere in his travels. Due to a quick intervention on the part of the Pilgrims&apos; sensei, the jester&apos;s plan never came to pass but he still carries the trumpet and it might be possible to convince him to part with it.</string>
<string name="110472">Arden Swift, patron of the Hellbreath Tavern and itinerant jester currently taveling with the entourage of githzerai Pilgrims, has placed his beloved Trumpet of Pandemonium as a prize for an upcoming card game. He had intended to use the trumpet to wake the so-called Sleeping Man but had been caught red-handed by the Pilgrims&apos; sensei before he could sound its blast. If you&apos;re interested in acquiring it for yourself, you merely have to place your ante on the table and guess the card he&apos;s holding in five questions or less. You&apos;re not entirely sure if you can trust him but it might be worth a try.</string>
<string name="110473">The familiar blackness of death enveloped you but the blood-red eyes of your betrayer, Mephistopheles, lingered to the end. And then you woke to find your eyes reflected in the Reaper&apos;s shimmering skin. Everything seems strangely familiar...</string>
<string name="110474">The archdevil Mephistopheles has played you for a fool. He has commanded your mysterious ally, the Reaper, to bar your return to Waterdeep in your homeworld of Toril, trapping you instead in some hellish world called Cania. The Reaper seems sympathetic to your plight but claims he has no choice but to obey for Mephistopheles has commanded him by his True Name. Such names seem to have a strange power in this place and it seems the only way to break Mephistopheles&apos; prohibition will be learn the Reaper&apos;s True Name for yourself.</string>
<string name="110475">Your search for the Reaper&apos;s True Name has turned up its first clue: one of the citizens of this strange city claims that an old and venerable creature known as the Sleeping Man might have the information your looking for. He sleeps in the city&apos;s northwest quarter and apparently has done so for longer than anyone can remember. Hopefully, with his help, you&apos;ll be able to return home to Waterdeep and take your vengeance on the archdevil Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110476">The Sleeping Man was not as helpful in your quest for the Reaper&apos;s True Name as you had hoped. You did learn, however, of an ancient race called the Knowers that populated Cania before it was colonized by the legions of hell. One of them, the Knower of Names, was banished by Mephistopheles to an unknown prison deep in Cania&apos;s frozen wastelands. Unable to find the Knower of Names, the Sleeping Man instead sought out her sister, the Knower of Places, with the help of a magical ring that that served as his guide through Cania&apos;s wastes. If you can repeat his feat, perhaps she will be able to help you find her sister&apos;s hidden prison. The Sleeping Man broke the ring into three parts and hid it in a guarded vault below his chambers. It seems your journey will begin there.</string>
<string name="110477">The Sleeping Man&apos;s ring that will lead you to the Knower of Places and hopefully to the Reaper&apos;s True Name is a strange artifact indeed. When you slip it onto your finger, it is as if you can see into another sort of space, another dimension. Some things are present there that are not present in the real world and some things you would expect to find have disappeared. According to the Sleeping Man, the ring will be most helpful in the out of doors where a line of glowing arrows will apparently chart a safe course for you through Cania&apos;s vast wastelands. You feel the stirrings of hope in your chest for the first time since Mephistopheles banished you to this frozen place.</string>
<string name="110478">Tormented by her loneliness, the Knower of Places has agreed to help you on your quest for the Reaper&apos;s True Name. She has woven a new magic into the Sleeping Man&apos;s ring, allowing it to guide you to her sister, the Knower of Names, just as it guided you to her. She left you with a cryptic parting message that will hopefully aid you when you reach her sister&apos;s icy prison: &quot;Time is a twelve-spoked wheel and with every hour of our lives another spoke has come and gone. In the passing of seven spokes a hole was dug and a fearsome devil freed. Had the digging been done but sixteen spokes the sooner, it would have uncovered what you need.&quot; Hopefully you&apos;ll be able to compel the Reaper to return you to Waterdeep before Mephistopheles has destroyed your home forever.</string>
<string name="110479">At long last you have learned the True Name of the Reaper: Hecugoth the Abandoned. You say it aloud a few times, rolling it around on your tongue. It has a sad sound to it but you are eager to put it to use. It&apos;s your ticket out of here, back to Waterdeep and your homeworld of Toril... or whatever still remains of them after the chaos that Mephistopheles has sown in your absence. The Knower of Names will take you back to the Gates of Cania but you pause to consider whether you have any pressing tasks you wish to accomplish on this plane before you go. Facing Mephistopheles won&apos;t be easy and you&apos;d better have made your peace with the world.</string>
<string name="110480">Commanded by his True Name, the Reaper has opened a Planar Gate that will lead you back home to Waterdeep. Mephistopheles won&apos;t be expecting you so you&apos;ll have to take advantage of whatever element of surprise you have. It will pay to be well-prepared before you step through that gate.</string>
<string name="110481">Peering into an ice crystal that thrust itself up from Cania&apos;s glacial floor, you saw a vision of Mephistopheles&apos; progress in your homeworld of Toril. It appears that he has discovered the carnage you left behind at the Rebel Camp. As he passed through the rotting carcasses, they rose in his wake, a ghostly army bound to do his bidding...</string>
<string name="110482">A group of disconsolate Pilgrims are trapped in Cania much like you. Their leader, the sensei, led them here to worship at the feet of a figure they refer to as the Sleeping Man. She can be found in the Temple in the city&apos;s northwest corner.</string>
<string name="110483">Dharvana, the githzerai sensei, insists that you must learn and recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man before she will let you into the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see him. She listed the Five-Fold Mysteries as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?</string>
<string name="110484">Before you may enter the Temple of the Sleeping Man&apos;s Inner Sanctum, you must learn the Five-Fold Mysteries and recite them to Dharvana, the githzerai sensei. The Five-Fold Mysteries are as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?

You have learned the answer to one of those five Mysteries.</string>
<string name="110485">Dharvana, the githzerai sensei, insists that you must learn and recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man before she will let you into the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see him. She listed the Five-Fold Mysteries as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?

You have now learned the answer to two of those five Mysteries.</string>
<string name="110486">Dharvana, the githzerai sensei, insists that you must learn and recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man before she will let you into the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see him. She listed the Five-Fold Mysteries as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?

You have now learned the answer to three of those five Mysteries.</string>
<string name="110487">Dharvana, the githzerai sensei, insists that you must learn and recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man before she will let you into the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see him. She listed the Five-Fold Mysteries as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?

You have now learned the answer to four of those five Mysteries.</string>
<string name="110488">Dharvana, the githzerai sensei, insists that you must learn and recite the Five-Fold Mysteries of the Sleeping Man before she will let you into the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum to see him. She listed the Five-Fold Mysteries as follows: Who is he? From where did he come? Why did he leave? Who did he seek? What was the answer?

You have now learned the answer to all five of those Mysteries, should you wish to recite them before the Sensei.</string>
<string name="110489">There, in the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum, with the winged form of the Sleeping Man prostrate before you, you tried in vain to make use of the sensei&apos;s amulet. The crystal glowed a murky green when in his presence and you could feel its growing hum but you somehow lacked the wisdom to tap into its psionic powers. </string>
<string name="110490">There, in the temple&apos;s Inner Sanctum, with the winged form of the Sleeping Man prostrate before you, you made use of the sensei&apos;s amulet. The crystal glowed a murky green when in his presence and you could feel its growing hum and then, all at once, you found yourself swept up within his dreams. </string>
<string name="110491">There, in the temple&apos;s dim green light, the sensei&apos;s amulet clasped about your neck, you dreamed the dreams of the Sleeping Man. Mephistopheles was there and a woman called the Knower of Names, whom he banished. And an older woman, the Knower of Places, whom the Sleeping Man had visited in search of his one true love. Throughout his quest, he was somehow guided by a ring that now lies, buried and guarded, in a chamber below him. If you hope to find the Knowers, you will need that ring upon your finger...</string>
<string name="110492">There, in the temple&apos;s dim green light, you have done the unthinkable and woken the Sleeping Man. Hopefully he will be able to tell you the Reaper&apos;s True Name.</string>
<string name="110493">In waking the Sleeping Man, you unleashed the sensei&apos;s fury. Driven mad with rage, she attacked and you had no choice but to defend yourself. Now she lies dead at the feet of the Sleeping Man who she worshiped. You decide you should keep her amulet as something to remember her by.</string>
<string name="110494">The Sleeping Man knows many things but, sadly, the Reaper&apos;s True Name is not one of them. Even so, he tells of a race of creatures called the Knowers who once called Cania home. One of them, the Knower of Names was banished by Mephistopheles long ago while the other, the Knower of Places, lives in hiding deep in Cania&apos;s frozen wastelands. His own quest had brought him the latter&apos;s hidden lair, long ago, a feat made possible only with the aid of an enchanted ring. The ring lies in a chamber under the temple, guarded and kept safe all these many years. He has invited you to make use of the ring, provided you can claim it, and wishes you well on your journey.</string>
<string name="110495">Mephistopheles left five Guardians to block the Sleeping Man&apos;s path. The two weakest were defeated in ages past and a third and fourth killed recently by your hands. You have now killed the fifth and final guardian, a wizardly Pit Fiend who stood guard over the prison itself, perhaps there to protect it from the Blood War that raged so close at hand. With all five Guardians dead, the Knower of Names is yours and her secrets too. Now if only you can find some way to free her from the ice.</string>
<string name="110496">You can feel yourself getting closer to the hidden lair of the Knower of Places. In a secret chamber deep in the icy wastes of Cania, you have found the statue of a gargoyle. Etched along its base in blue lettering are the words &quot;Stone to stone, the stone turns. Lightning to lightning, the lightning fades.&quot;</string>
<string name="110497">A series of chambers run deep beneath the ice of Cania, leading to what you hope will be the hidden lair of the Knower of Places. Various obstacles have stood in your way but now a portal has appeared, leading into a third chamber that lies beyond. </string>
<string name="110498">As you peer at the sensei&apos;s amulet, you notice that the light seems to play strangely off its crystalline structure. Not quite sure what to make of this strange behavior, you return it to your pack for later investigation.</string>
<string name="110499">In a fortunate twist of fate, the sensei&apos;s amulet has revealed its true nature. By carefully controlling the angle at which the light strikes its crystalline structure, you find that the resulting refraction has the unexpected ability to modify your body&apos;s form. You file the knowledge away for future reference. From here on in, you decide to be more a little more mindful of your magic items, that they don&apos;t trigger again so unexpectedly.</string>
<string name="110500">True Names: Reaper</string>
<string name="110501">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Reaper of Cania and can finally command him to send you home to the Prime Material. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Hecugoth the Abandoned.</string>
<string name="110502">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Reaper of Cania. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Hecugoth the Abandoned. You recently used this knowledge to command him to let the Githzerai Pilgrims return to their home plane of Limbo.</string>
<string name="110503">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Reaper of Cania. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Hecugoth the Abandoned. You recently used this knowledge to command him to allow the Spirits of the Dead to pass through the Gates and haunt the Land of the Living.</string>
<string name="110504">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Reaper of Cania. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Hecugoth the Abandoned. You recently used this knowledge to command him to loose the Devils of Cania upon the unsuspecting planes.</string>
<string name="110505">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of the Reaper of Cania. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Hecugoth the Abandoned. You recently used it to command him to let you return home to Waterdeep to take your vengeance on the arch-devil Mephistopheles.</string>
<string name="110506">Having paid the Knower&apos;s price, you have learned the True Name of your henchman Valen. He is known in the gods&apos; tongue as Oeskathine the Demonwrestler.

Empowered by this knowledge, you recently freed him from his demonic taint.</string>
<string name="110507">This hastily scrawled note bears Mephistopheles&apos; now-familiar script:

&quot;I am about to make my move and lay claim to Toril. Perhaps the Tanar&apos;ri have caught wind of this for I have just received word that they are launching an assault near where I have stationed you. Stray catapult fire from the battle has already melted through the ice and freed one of my treacherous generals. Make your way to the prison and fend the Tanar&apos;ri off at all costs. The last thing I need is some fool demon getting his paws on my Knower of Names. Serve me well and I may give you lordship over Waterdeep once it is mine...&quot;

It appears that this particular front of the Blood War was opened just before he left for your homeworld, Toril. </string>
<string name="110508">Deepest Wastes of Cania</string>
<string name="110509">Beneath the Ice</string>
<string name="110510">Ice-Bound Lair</string>
<string name="110511">h2_spirit_genmal_dw_rw_rs020</string>
<string name="110512">h2_spirit_genfem_dw_rw_rs020</string>
<string name="110513">h2_spirit_genmal_dw_rw_rs040</string>
<string name="110514">h2_spirit_genfem_dw_rw_rs040</string>
<string name="110515">Tendrils of magic bar your way. Beyond them you can hear a woman&apos;s sobs. Her voice, hollow and cold, echoes off the icy walls of her self-imposed prison.</string>
<string name="110516">Wastes of Cania</string>
<string name="110517">Worg Den</string>
<string name="110518">Tributary of the River Styx</string>
<string name="110519">Dark as a gathering storm, something about Aribeth&apos;s armor fills you with dread.</string>
<string name="110520">Aribeth&apos;s lovingly polished armor gleams in the dim light, keeping the darkness of the place at bay.</string>
<string name="110521">Ferron, leader of the rebel golems, is dead.</string>
<string name="110522">Aghaaz, leader of the Maker&apos;s golems, is dead.</string>
<string name="110523"></string>
<string name="110524">Read</string>
<string name="110525">Drink potion</string>
<string name="110526">Meditate</string>
<string name="110527">Worship</string>
<string name="110528">Sit on ground</string>
<string name="110529">Fall down backwards</string>
<string name="110530">Fall down forwards</string>
<string name="110531">Coming Soon</string>
<string name="110532"></string>
<string name="110533"></string>
<string name="110534">Sea Hag</string>
<string name="110535">A horrible creature, its flesh is sickly and yellow, covered with warts and oozing sores. Its long, filthy hair resembles rotting seaweed.</string>
<string name="110536">Sea Hag Properties</string>
<string name="110537">Evil Eye</string>
<string name="110538">Horrific Appearance</string>
<string name="110539">Could not load the Module.
Missing required custom talk table.</string>
<string name="110540">Could not load the Module.
There was an error loading the module.</string>
<string name="110541">Custom Talk Table</string>
<string name="110542"></string>
<string name="110543">Water with walkmesh</string>
<string name="110544"></string>
<string name="110545"></string>
<string name="110546">Ant Hill (sand)</string>
<string name="110547">Chessboard (sand)</string>
<string name="110548">Crystal (sand)</string>
<string name="110549">Field (sand)</string>
<string name="110550">Granary (sand)</string>
<string name="110551">Graves 1 (sand)</string>
<string name="110552">Graves 2 (sand)</string>
<string name="110553">Graves 3 (sand)</string>
<string name="110554">Graves 4 (sand)</string>
<string name="110555">Graves 5 (sand)</string>
<string name="110556">House 1 (sand)</string>
<string name="110557">House 2 (sand)</string>
<string name="110558">Mausoleum 1 (sand)</string>
<string name="110559">Mausoleum 2 (sand)</string>
<string name="110560">Menhir (sand)</string>
<string name="110561">Portal (sand)</string>
<string name="110562">Shrine 1 (sand)</string>
<string name="110563"></string>
<string name="110564">Shrine 2 (sand)</string>
<string name="110565">Tower (sand)</string>
<string name="110566">Tree (sand)</string>
<string name="110567">Tree Hollow (sand)</string>
<string name="110568">Warzone 1 (sand)</string>
<string name="110569">Warzone 2 (sand)</string>
<string name="110570">Well (sand)</string>
<string name="110571">Barn 1 (sand) 2x2</string>
<string name="110572">Barn 2 (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110573">Barn 3 (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110574">Barracks (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110575">Dragon Skeleton (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110576">Farm 1 (sand) 2x2</string>
<string name="110577">Farm 2 (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110578">Farm 3 (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110579">Inn (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110580">Temple Evil (sand) 3x2</string>
<string name="110581">Temple Good (sand) 3x2</string>
<string name="110582">Temple Neutral (sand) 2x2</string>
<string name="110583">Tower (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110584">Warzone (sand) 1x2</string>
<string name="110585">Windmill (sand) 2x2</string>
<string name="110586">Tropical</string>
<string name="110587">Sand</string>
<string name="110588">Lighthouse</string>
<string name="110589">Warship 1x3</string>
<string name="110590">Merchant Galley 1x3</string>
<string name="110591">Play Demo</string>
<string name="110592">Please wait while we authenticate your Premium Neverwinter Nights Module. This may take a few minutes.

If you don&apos;t own this module, you can press the &apos;Play Demo&apos; button to view the Demo section of this module.</string>
<string name="110593">Premium Neverwinter Nights Module Information</string>
<string name="110594"></string>
<string name="110595"></string>
<string name="110596">Ship - Front</string>
<string name="110597">Dock with Plank</string>
<string name="110598">Ship - Front (Dockable)</string>
<string name="110599">Ship - Middle</string>
<string name="110600">Ship - Middle (Dockable)</string>
<string name="110601">Ship - Back</string>
<string name="110602">Merchant Ship - Front</string>
<string name="110603">Merchant Ship - Front (Dockable)</string>
<string name="110604">Merchant Ship - Middle</string>
<string name="110605">Merchant Ship - Middle (Dockable)</string>
<string name="110606">Merchant Ship - Back</string>
<string name="110607">Shore with Ship Dock</string>
<string name="110608">Weathered Ship - Back</string>
<string name="110609">Weathered Ship - Front</string>
<string name="110610">Weathered Ship - Middle</string>
<string name="110611">darthiir</string>
<string name="110612">hargluk</string>
<string name="110613">sakphul</string>
<string name="110614">yingil</string>
<string name="110615">tu&apos;rilthiir</string>
<string name="110616">cretok</string>
<string name="110617">rivvil</string>
<string name="110618">jalil</string>
<string name="110619">jaluk</string>
<string name="110620"></string>
<string name="110621">Sea Hag</string>
<string name="110622">Error 110622 - You are not authorized to play this Premium Neverwinter Nights Module. If you feel this message is in error, please see http://support.bioware.com/ for more information.</string>
<string name="110623">Error 110623 - Authentication of this Premium Neverwinter Nights Module has failed. You will now be taken to the Demo section of the module. If you feel this message is in error, please see http://support.bioware.com/ for more information.</string>
<string name="110624">Saving is disabled while playing this DEMO module.</string>
<string name="110625"></string>
<string name="110626">Merchant Ship - Middle (with plank)</string>
<string name="110627">Premium Neverwinter Nights Modules require that you authenticate with the BioWare Master Server to verify your ownership of this module. If you do not have an active connection to the internet or the BioWare Master Server cannot be reached due to a firewall or proxy, you will only be able to play the Demo portion of this Premium Neverwinter Nights Module.

If you need assistance, please visit http://support.bioware.com/</string>
<string name="110628">Error 110628 - You are not authorized to play this Premium Neverwinter Nights Module. If you feel this message is in error, please see http://support.bioware.com/ for more information.</string>
<string name="110629">Error 110629 - You do not own the Premium Neverwinter Nights Module running on the server that you are attempting to connect to. You must have this module installed in order to play. If you feel this message is in error, please see http://support.bioware.com/ for more information.</string>
<string name="110630">Please wait while we authenticate your Premium Neverwinter Nights Module. This may take a few minutes.</string>
<string name="110631">Could not load the Module.
Module file might be corrupt OR an error occurred
authenticating ownership of this Premium Neverwinter 
Nights Module.</string>
<string name="110632"></string>
<string name="110633">There was an error generating your character file.</string>
<string name="110634">Water with walkmesh (alternate height)</string>
<string name="110635">Bulette</string>
<string name="110636">Troglodyte</string>
<string name="110637">Troglodyte Warrior</string>
<string name="110638">Troglodyte Cleric</string>
<string name="110639">Aptly called a &quot;landshark,&quot; the bulette is a terrifying predator that lives only to eat.</string>
<string name="110640">Troglodytes are cave-dwelling reptilian humanoids who take pleasure in fighting battles and in eating the bodies of their dead foes. While not very bright, trogs are known for their ferocity, cunning, and horrific stench.</string>
<string name="110641">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt; emits a nauseating stench.</string>
<string name="110642">When a Troglodyte is angry or frightened it secretes an oily, musk like chemical that nearly every form 
of animal life finds offensive. 

All creatures (except Troglodytes) within 30 ft must succeed at a Fortitude save (DC 13) or be overcome with nausea. 
This lasts for 10 rounds and deals 1d6 points of temporary Strength damage. 
</string>
<string name="110643">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt; has horrific appearance.</string>
<string name="110644">A Sea Hag&apos;s appearance is so revolting that those setting eyes upon the Hag
must make a Fortitude save (DC 11) or temporarily lose 2d8 points of strength.</string>
<string name="110645">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt; uses evil eye gaze.</string>
<string name="110646">A dire gaze can be cast upon any single creature within 30 feet.
The target must succeed at a Fortitude save (DC 11).
Creatures who fail lose 5 points from both strength and constitution and
also have a 25% chance of losing 5 points from all ability scores due to fright.
</string>
<string name="110647">Troglodyte Stench</string>
<string name="110648">Difficulty Slider : Very Easy</string>
<string name="110649">Difficulty Slider : Easy</string>
<string name="110650">Difficulty Slider : Normal</string>
<string name="110651">Difficulty Slider : D&amp;D Hardcore Rules</string>
<string name="110652">Difficulty Slider : Very Difficult</string>
<string name="110653">PM - Kingmaker Theme</string>
<string name="110654">PM - ShadowGuard Theme</string>
<string name="110655">PM - Witch&apos;s Wake Theme</string>
<string name="110656">Weathered Ship - Undockable</string>
<string name="110657">Weathered Ship - Ship to Grass</string>
<string name="110658">Weathered Ship - Ship to Dock</string>
<string name="110659">Weathered Ship Merchant Ship docked together</string>
<string name="110660">Merchant Ship - Undockable</string>
<string name="110661">Merchant Ship - Ship to grass</string>
<string name="110662">Merchant Ship - Ship to Dock</string>
<string name="110663">The game server that you are connecting to was unable to verify your password. The game server has opted to not allow players to join unless their password can be verified. Please try again later.</string>
<string name="110664">Failed to cast spell. Client and Server spell information doesn&apos;t match.</string>
<string name="110665">Test Module</string>
<string name="110666">Weathered Ship - Ship to Sand</string>
<string name="110667">Merchant Ship - Ship to Sand</string>
<string name="110668">Ship Crosser Type</string>
<string name="110669">Shipwreck 3x3</string>
<string name="110670">Hot Springs</string>
<string name="110671">Cave Pool w/ Barrier</string>
<string name="110672">Parrot</string>
<string name="110673">Midnight Rose Ship</string>
<string name="110674">Galleon Ship undock</string>
<string name="110675">Galleon Ship Docked</string>
<string name="110676">Galleon Ship ship to grass</string>
<string name="110677">Galleon Ship ship to sand</string>
<string name="110678">Galleon Ship with Weathered Ship</string>
<string name="110679">Galleon Ship with Merchant Ship</string>
<string name="110680">Sea Caves</string>
<string name="110681">Tile Floor</string>
<string name="110682">Bludgeoning and Piercing</string>
<string name="110683">Minimize Toolset on test module</string>
<string name="110684">Seagull</string>
<string name="110685">Shark</string>
<string name="110686">Could not connect to Master Server, some multiplayer services may not be available.
Unable to establish a valid UDP port.</string>
<string name="110687">Eye of Gruumsh</string>
<string name="110688">Eyes of Gruumsh</string>
<string name="110689">eye of Gruumsh</string>
<string name="110690">(PRESTIGE CLASS)
Worshipers of the Orc deity Gruumsh that have put out their own right eye in a bloody and painful ritual. These living martyrs to Gruumsh are some of the toughest orcs and half-orcs in the world.
The eye of Gruumsh is a true prestige class in the sense that all orcs respect those who achieve it.
Barbarians gain the most value from this prestige class, since it encourages raging as a fighting style

- Hit Die: d12
- Proficiencies: Simple and Martial Weapons, Light, and Medium Armor Proficiency, Shields
- Skill Points: 2 + Int Modifier.

REQUIREMENTS:

Alignment: Chaotic evil, choatic neutral, or neutral evil.
Race: Half-Orc or Orc
Feats: Exotic Weapon Proficiency (Double Axe), Weapon Focus (Double Axe).
Base Attack Bonus: +6

ABILITIES:

Level
1: Blind-Fight.
  Command the Horde
  Rage 1/day.
2. Swing Blindly - The character&apos;s rage&apos;s become more powerful granting a +4 strength bonus, while also suffering a -4 armor bonus while raging.
3: Ritual Scarring - Through frequent disfiguration of his own skin, the eye of Gruumsh gains a +1 natural armor bonus.
4: Blinding Spittle - The character can spit their stomach acid into a target&apos;s eyes 2/day.
  Rage 2/day.
5: Blindsight - The character gains blindsight in a 5 foot radius.
6: Ritual Scarring - The eye of Gruumsh&apos;s natural armor bonus increases to +2.
7: Blinding Spittle 4/day.
8: Blindsight 10 foot radius.
  Rage 3/day.
9: Ritual Scarring - The eye of Gruumsh&apos;s natural armor bonus increases to +3.
10: Sight of Gruumsh - The character gains a +2 morale bonus on all saving throws.</string>
<string name="110691">Blinding Spittle</string>
<string name="110692">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 4.
Specifics: At 4th level, an Eye of Gruumsh can launch blinding spittle at any opponent within 20 feet. Using a ranged touch attack (at a -4 penalty), he spits his stomach acid into the target&apos;s eyes. An opponent who fails a Reflex save (DC 10 + eye of Gruumsh level + eye of Gruumsh&apos;s Constitution bonus) is blinded until he or she can rinse away the spittle. This attack has no effect on creatures that don&apos;t have eyes or don&apos;t depend on vision.  Blinding spittle is usable 2/day at 4th level and 4/day at 7th level.
Use: Combat Mode.</string>
<string name="110693">Command the Horde</string>
<string name="110694">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 1.
Specifics: At 1st level, the Eye of Gruumsh may grant a +2 morale bonus on Will saving throws to any nongood orcs or half-orcs with Hit Dice lower than his character level within 30 feet. The effect lasts for 1 hour per eye of Gruumsh level.
Use: Combat Mode.</string>
<string name="110695">Swing Blindly</string>
<string name="110696">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 2.
Specifics: At 2nd level, the Eye of Gruumsh&apos;s rage ability becomes more powerful at the cost of lower defenses. The character gains an additional +4 bonus to his strength score while raging, while his armor class penalty increases to -4.
Use: Combat Mode.</string>
<string name="110697">Ritual Scarring</string>
<string name="110698">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 3.
Specifics: Through frequent disfiguration of his own skin, the eye of Gruumsh gains a +1 natural armor bonus at 3rd level. This bonus increases by +1 for every three eye of Gruumsh levels gained thereafter.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110699">Blindsight, 5 foot radius</string>
<string name="110700">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 5.
Specifics: At 5th level, the Eye of Gruumsh gains blindsight in a 5 foot radius. Using hearing the eye of Gruumsh maneuvers and fights as well as a sighted creature. Invisibility and darkness are irrelevant within this range. The eye of Gruumsh does not need to make Spot or Listen checks to notice creatures within range of his blindsight ability.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110701">Blindsight, 10 foot radius</string>
<string name="110702">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 8.
Specifics: At 8th level, the Eye of Gruumsh gains blindsight in a 10 foot radius. Using hearing the eye of Gruumsh maneuvers and fights as well as a sighted creature. Invisibility and darkness are irrelevant within this range. The eye of Gruumsh does not need to make Spot or Listen checks to notice creatures within range of his blindsight ability.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110703">Sight of Gruumsh</string>
<string name="110704">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Eye of Gruumsh level 10.
Specifics: At 10th level, the Eye of Gruumsh sees the moment of his own death through his missing eye. This foreknowledge gives him a +2 morale bonus on all saving throws from then on.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110705">Blindsight, 60 foot radius</string>
<string name="110706">Type of Feat: General
Prerequisite: None.
Specifics: Using nonvisual senses, such as sensitivity to vibrations, scent, acute hearing, or echolocation, the creature maneuvers and fights as well as a sighted creature. Invisibility and darkness are irrelevant. The creature usually does not need to make Spot or Listen checks to notice creatures within range of its blindsight ability.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110707">Shou Disciple</string>
<string name="110708">Shou Disciples</string>
<string name="110709">Shou disciple</string>
<string name="110710">(PRESTIGE CLASS)
Shou disciples are martial artists who have studied or observed the monks of Kara-Tur and seek to emulate their style. Focusing more on the martial aspects of a monk&apos;s training, they sacrifice the enlightenment and supernatural abilities of the true ascetic. Shou disciples fight with martial weapons and often wear armor, instantly marking them as different from monks.

- Hit Die: d10
- Proficiencies: Martial and Monk Weapons, Light Armor Proficiency.
- Skill Points: 2 + Int Modifier.

REQUIREMENTS:

Feats: Dodge, Improved Unarmed Strike, Weapon Focus (Unarmed Strike)
Base Attack Bonus: +3
Skills: Tumble 4 ranks
Base Reflex Save: +2

ABILITIES:

Level
1: Shou Disciple Dodge Bonus +1 (replaces the normal +1 dodge feat bonus).
  Unarmed Strike - The character deals 1d6 of unarmed damage. A Shou disciple with levels in the monk class will use the better of the two damage ranges, or the unarmed damage calculated by combining his Shou disciple and monk levels and using the unarmed damage of a monk of the resulting level if it produces a better result.
  Wearing light armor does not interfere with any of the Shou disciple&apos;s class abilities, but shields and medium or heavy armor do.
2: Unarmed Strike - The character deals 1d8 of unarmed damage. 
  Shou Disciple Dodge Bonus +2 
  Bonus Feat - Chosen from the following list if the prerequisites are met: Deflect Arrows, Expertise, Improved Initiative, Improved Knockdown, Mobility, Power Attack, Spring Attack, Weapon Finesse and Weapon Specialization.
3: Unarmed Strike - The character deals 1d10 of unarmed damage.  
  Martial Flurry (light) - The character gains the ability to use any light melee weapon for his flurry of blows.
4: Shou Disciple Dodge Bonus +3 
  Bonus Feat - Chosen from the following list if the prerequisites are met: Deflect Arrows, Expertise, Improved Initiative, Improved Knockdown, Mobility, Power Attack, Spring Attack, Weapon Finesse and Weapon Specialization.
5: Unarmed Strike - The character deals 2d6 of unarmed damage. 
  Martial Flurry (any) - The character gains the ability to use any melee weapon for his flurry of blows.
</string>
<string name="110711">Dodge Bonus + 2</string>
<string name="110712">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Shou Disciple level 2.
Specifics: Shou disciples are highly trained at dodging blows, giving the Shou disciple a +2 dodge bonus for his Dodge feat at 2nd level . A condition that makes the Shou disciple lose his Dexiterity bonus to armor class also makes him lose this dodge bonus.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="110713">Dodge Bonus + 3</string>
<string name="110714">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Shou Disciple level 4.
Specifics: Shou disciples are highly trained at dodging blows, giving the Shou disciple a +3 dodge bonus for his Dodge feat at 4th level . A condition that makes the Shou disciple lose his Dexiterity bonus to armor class also makes him lose this dodge bonus.
Use: Automatic.
</string>
<string name="110715">Martial Flurry (light)</string>
<string name="110716">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Shou Disciple level 3.
Specifics: At 3rd level, a Shou disciple gains the ability to use any light melee weapon for his flurry of blows, not just Kamas.
Use: Combat Mode.</string>
<string name="110717">Martial Flurry (any)</string>
<string name="110718">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Shou Disciple level 5.
Specifics: At 5th level, a Shou disciple may use any melee weapon for his flurry of blows.
Use: Combat Mode.</string>
<string name="110719">Give Alignment Shift</string>
<string name="110720">Give Good Alignment Shift</string>
<string name="110721">Give Evil Alignment Shift</string>
<string name="110722">Give Lawful Alignment Shift</string>
<string name="110723">Give Chaotic Alignment Shift</string>
<string name="110724">You are too large to equip that item.</string>
<string name="110725">PM - Pirates Theme</string>
<string name="110726">PM - Pirates Theme Variation</string>
<string name="110727">Set random facing</string>
<string name="110728">Mako Shark</string>
<string name="110729">Hammerhead Shark</string>
<string name="110730">Goblin Shark</string>
<string name="110731">Shark, Mako</string>
<string name="110732">Shark, Hammerhead</string>
<string name="110733">Shark, Goblin</string>
<string name="110734">Shark Hide</string>
<string name="110735">Shark Bite 1d8 (+1)</string>
<string name="110736">Seagull, flying</string>
<string name="110737">Seagull, walking</string>
<string name="110738">Seagull Feather</string>
<string name="110739">Ochre Jelly, Large</string>
<string name="110740">Ochre Jelly, Medium</string>
<string name="110741">Ochre Jelly, Small</string>
<string name="110742">Gray Ooze</string>
<string name="110743">Gray Ooze Slam</string>
<string name="110744">Gray Ooze Properties</string>
<string name="110745">Ochre Jelly Slam (hard)</string>
<string name="110746">Ochre Jelly Slam (medium)</string>
<string name="110747">Ochre Jelly Slam (easy)</string>
<string name="110748">Ochre Jelly Properties (hard)</string>
<string name="110749">Ochre Jelly Properties (medium)</string>
<string name="110750">Ochre Jelly Properties (easy)</string>
<string name="110751">Ichor</string>
<string name="110752">Sahuagin</string>
<string name="110753">Sahuagin Cleric</string>
<string name="110754">Sahuagin Leader</string>
<string name="110755">Bubbles, Small</string>
<string name="110756">Bubbles, Large</string>
<string name="110757">Bubbles, Medium</string>
<string name="110758">Chest, Sunken</string>
<string name="110759">Chest, Buried</string>
<string name="110760">Raft</string>
<string name="110761">Raft, Broken</string>
<string name="110762">Rope Coil 1</string>
<string name="110763">Rope Coil 2</string>
<string name="110764">Palm Tree 1</string>
<string name="110765">Palm Tree 2</string>
<string name="110766">Driftwood 1</string>
<string name="110767">Driftwood 2</string>
<string name="110768">Driftwood 3</string>
<string name="110769">Driftwood 4</string>
<string name="110770">Starfish</string>
<string name="110771">Dwarf Bed</string>
<string name="110772">Dwarf Bench</string>
<string name="110773">Dwarf Chair</string>
<string name="110774">Dwarf Table</string>
<string name="110775">Mushroom 1</string>
<string name="110776">Mushroom 2</string>
<string name="110777">Mushroom 3</string>
<string name="110778">Mushroom 4</string>
<string name="110779">Troglodyte Bed</string>
<string name="110780">Troglodyte Egg</string>
<string name="110781">Troglodyte Nest</string>
<string name="110782">Troglodyte Throne</string>
<string name="110783">Troglodyte Shrine</string>
<string name="110784">Hanging Dwarf Skeleton</string>
<string name="110785">Candle 1</string>
<string name="110786">Candle 2</string>
<string name="110787">Candle 1 (No Ambient Light)</string>
<string name="110788">Candle 2 (No Ambient Light)</string>
<string name="110789">Footprint, Left</string>
<string name="110790">Footprint, Right</string>
<string name="110791">Puddle 1</string>
<string name="110792">Puddle 2</string>
<string name="110793">Portal 2</string>
<string name="110794">Shrine of Umberlee</string>
<string name="110795">Shrine of Umberlee (No Ambient Light)</string>
<string name="110796">Flag, Pirate</string>
<string name="110797">Flag, Umberlee</string>
<string name="110798">Parrot</string>
<string name="110799">Chair, Sea</string>
<string name="110800">Table, Sea</string>
<string name="110801">Sea Idol</string>
<string name="110802">Net</string>
<string name="110803">Obelisk, Sea</string>
<string name="110804">Sea Shell 1</string>
<string name="110805">Sea Shell 2</string>
<string name="110806">Load Premium Neverwinter Nights Module</string>
<string name="110807">Sea Shell 3</string>
<string name="110808">Fungus</string>
<string name="110809">Rock 1</string>
<string name="110810">Rock 2</string>
<string name="110811">Rock 3</string>
<string name="110812">Rock 4</string>
<string name="110813">Rock 5</string>
<string name="110814">Fish 1</string>
<string name="110815">Fish 2</string>
<string name="110816">Fish 3</string>
<string name="110817">Pirate &apos;X&apos;</string>
<string name="110818">Arrow, Red</string>
<string name="110819">Arrow, Green</string>
<string name="110820">Arrow, Blue</string>
<string name="110821">Arrow, Yellow</string>
<string name="110822">Arrow, Magenta</string>
<string name="110823">Arrow, Cyan</string>
<string name="110824">Arrow, Orange</string>
<string name="110825">Arrow, White</string>
<string name="110826">Kelp, Type 1, Large</string>
<string name="110827">Kelp, Type 1, Medium</string>
<string name="110828">Kelp, Type 1, Small</string>
<string name="110829">Kelp, Type 2, Large</string>
<string name="110830">Kelp, Type 2, Medium</string>
<string name="110831">Kelp, Type 2, Small</string>
<string name="110832">Kelp, Type 3, Large</string>
<string name="110833">Kelp, Type 3, Medium</string>
<string name="110834">Kelp, Type 3, Small</string>
<string name="110835">Ochre Jelly</string>
<string name="110836">Bubbles</string>
<string name="110837">Candle</string>
<string name="110838">Driftwood</string>
<string name="110839">School of Fish</string>
<string name="110840">Flag</string>
<string name="110841">Footprint</string>
<string name="110842">Kelp</string>
<string name="110843">Rope Coil</string>
<string name="110844">Sea Shell</string>
<string name="110845">Puddle</string>
<string name="110846">This three-tined variation of a spear is a favored weapon of some undersea humanoids.</string>
<string name="110847">Reaching anywhere from 9 to 13 feet long, the Mako is one of the most terrifying hunters of the sea. Renowned for its speed and ability to really freak the heck out of anyone who thought it was a good idea to go swimming even after that old fisherman guy said that was a bad idea.</string>
<string name="110848">A relentless and cold killer whose unusual head shape allows for greater maneuverability in close quarters. Its ability to detect prey by smell is nearly ten times as sensitive as its shark brothers and thus makes a point showing off in front of all the girl sharks.</string>
<string name="110849">This extremely rare type of shark is distinctive for its long beak that protrudes out over its vicious jaws. Most adventurers when sighting a Goblin Shark for the first time are stunned by how deeply weird it looks and usually succumb to rows of pointed teeth soon after.</string>
<string name="110850">Highly intelligent coastal birds that have learned to co-exist with civilization in a scavenger role. Known for their distinctive squawks, white to gray coloring with black markings and distinct lack of toilette training.</string>
<string name="110851">Sometimes referred to as sea devils, sahuagin are marine predators that are superb underwater fighters as well as known for their midnight raids on the surface.</string>
<string name="110852">This amorphous creature resembles a harmless puddle of water.</string>
<string name="110853">This amorphous creature resembles a dark yellow amoeba.</string>
<string name="110854">Seaweed still clings to the salt-bleached wood.</string>
<string name="110855">Bubbles stream upwards from a small fissure in the sea floor. Whether they are a product of geothermal activity or some form of life that lurks below, you cannot tell.</string>
<string name="110856">A small candle floats on a driftwood plank.</string>
<string name="110857">Seashells and colored sands have been mixed in with the candlewax.</string>
<string name="110858">You wonder what desperate sea battle caused this treasure chest to be cast overboard, still unopened.</string>
<string name="110859">A hidden chest rises from the sands...</string>
<string name="110860">This is one of a variety of shells found in and around coastal regions.</string>
<string name="110861">A small school of fish darts about, seemingly oblivious to your presence.</string>
<string name="110862">Sometimes &apos;X&apos; does mark the spot.</string>
<string name="110863">This starfish has one more arm than you were expecting.</string>
<string name="110864">This shrine seems to be for the worship of some sort of aquatic god.</string>
<string name="110865">Skeletal remains adorn this barnacle-encrusted shrine.</string>
<string name="110866">You gaze at your reflection in the puddle. You look pretty good today, all things considered.</string>
<string name="110867">The clamshell that forms the back of this simple chair is bigger than any you&apos;ve ever seen.</string>
<string name="110868">The Jolly Roger grimaces at you from this tattered pennant.</string>
<string name="110869">This salt-stiffened pennant bears the parting waves of the sea goddess, Umberlee.</string>
<string name="110870">The parrot eyes you warily, stepping back and forth along its perch.</string>
<string name="110871">The kelp sways gently in the ocean current.</string>
<string name="110872">This fishing net has been strung out to dry.</string>
<string name="110873">This egg is large and heavy. You wonder what manner of creature lies dead or dormant within its shell.</string>
<string name="110874">A pair of brightly colored eggs rests in a nest of dried palm fronds.</string>
<string name="110875">This nest of palm fronds seems like it hasn&apos;t been occupied in a while.</string>
<string name="110876">This hempen rope has been carefully coiled to ensure it doesn&apos;t get tangled with future use.</string>
<string name="110877">Planking scraps protrude from this coil of hempen rope, clearly intended for some future use.</string>
<string name="110878">This simple raft is constructed of scrap logs and improvised ropes. It seems sturdy enough.</string>
<string name="110879">This simple raft was constructed of scrap logs and improvised ropes. It seemed sturdy enough until its encounter with this rock.</string>
<string name="110880">Barnacles encrust this weathered throne. The bones of its last occupant still call it home.</string>
<string name="110881">The skeleton of a small creature, probably a dwarf, sways in the breeze.</string>
<string name="110882">You don&apos;t quite recognize the creature depicted by this barnacle-encrusted statue but it&apos;s clearly aquatic in nature. The stone is old and deeply weathered.</string>
<string name="110883">Fossilized sea life lends some maritime charm to this beautiful marble table.</string>
<string name="110884">Barnacles encrust this small obelisk.</string>
<string name="110885">This small clump of fungus thrives in its dank surroundings.</string>
<string name="110886">Barnacles cling to these weathered stones.</string>
<string name="110887">Small and made of rock slabs; a bed that only a dwarf could love.</string>
<string name="110888">A small bench made of smooth rock.</string>
<string name="110889">This carved rock table is extremely smooth and polished.</string>
<string name="110890">This smooth chair has been carved out of solid rock slabs.</string>
<string name="110891">Weapon Focus (trident)</string>
<string name="110892">Weapon Specialization (trident)</string>
<string name="110893">Improved Critical (trident)</string>
<string name="110894">Devastating Critical (trident)</string>
<string name="110895">Epic Weapon Focus (trident)</string>
<string name="110896">Epic Weapon Specialization (trident)</string>
<string name="110897">Overwhelming Critical (trident)</string>
<string name="110898">Weapon of Choice (trident)</string>
<string name="110899">Base Damage: 1d8
Base Critical Threat: x2 
Base Damage Type: Piercing
Weapon Size: Large
Feats Required: Martial</string>
<string name="110900">OnPlayerChat</string>
<string name="110901">The OnPlayerChat Event fires whenever a player or DM types a text message into the talk channel. This event will not fire for private tell messages.</string>
<string name="110902">Dwarf mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110903">Dwarf mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110904">Elf mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110905">Elf mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110906">Gnome mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110907">Gnome mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110908">Halfling mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110909">Halfling mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110910">Half-Elf mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110911">Half-Elf mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110912">Half-Orc mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110913">Half-Orc mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110914">Human mounted, Female</string>
<string name="110915">Human mounted, Male</string>
<string name="110916">Horse, Walnut</string>
<string name="110917">Horse, Walnut, saddle</string>
<string name="110918">Horse, Walnut, saddle, packs</string>
<string name="110919">Horse, Walnut, leather barding</string>
<string name="110920">Horse, Walnut, scale mail barding</string>
<string name="110921">Horse, Walnut, chain barding</string>
<string name="110922">Horse, Walnut, purple barding</string>
<string name="110923">Horse, Walnut, red barding</string>
<string name="110924">Horse, Walnut, leather barding, packs</string>
<string name="110925">Horse, Walnut, scale mail barding, packs</string>
<string name="110926">Horse, Walnut, chain barding, packs</string>
<string name="110927">Horse, Walnut, purple barding, packs</string>
<string name="110928">Horse, Walnut, red barding, packs</string>
<string name="110929">Horse, Gunpowder</string>
<string name="110930">Horse, Gunpowder, saddle</string>
<string name="110931">Horse, Gunpowder, saddle, packs</string>
<string name="110932">Horse, Gunpowder, leather barding</string>
<string name="110933">Horse, Gunpowder, scale mail barding</string>
<string name="110934">Horse, Gunpowder, chain barding</string>
<string name="110935">Horse, Gunpowder, purple barding</string>
<string name="110936">Horse, Gunpowder, red barding</string>
<string name="110937">Horse, Gunpowder, leather barding, packs</string>
<string name="110938">Horse, Gunpowder, scale mail barding, packs</string>
<string name="110939">Horse, Gunpowder, chain barding, packs</string>
<string name="110940">Horse, Gunpowder, purple barding, packs</string>
<string name="110941">Horse, Gunpowder, red barding, packs</string>
<string name="110942">Horse, Spotted</string>
<string name="110943">Horse, Spotted, saddle</string>
<string name="110944">Horse, Spotted, saddle, packs</string>
<string name="110945">Horse, Spotted, leather barding</string>
<string name="110946">Horse, Spotted, scale mail barding</string>
<string name="110947">Horse, Spotted, chain barding</string>
<string name="110948">Horse, Spotted, purple barding</string>
<string name="110949">Horse, Spotted, red barding</string>
<string name="110950">Horse, Spotted, leather barding, packs</string>
<string name="110951">Horse, Spotted, scale mail barding, packs</string>
<string name="110952">Horse, Spotted, chain barding, packs</string>
<string name="110953">Horse, Spotted, purple barding, packs</string>
<string name="110954">Horse, Spotted, red barding, packs</string>
<string name="110955">Horse, Black</string>
<string name="110956">Horse, Black, saddle</string>
<string name="110957">Horse, Black, saddle, packs</string>
<string name="110958">Horse, Black, leather barding</string>
<string name="110959">Horse, Black, scale mail barding</string>
<string name="110960">Horse, Black, chain barding</string>
<string name="110961">Horse, Black, purple barding</string>
<string name="110962">Horse, Black, red barding</string>
<string name="110963">Horse, Black, leather barding, packs</string>
<string name="110964">Horse, Black, scale mail barding, packs</string>
<string name="110965">Horse, Black, chain barding, packs</string>
<string name="110966">Horse, Black, purple barding, packs</string>
<string name="110967">Horse, Black, red barding, packs</string>
<string name="110968">Nightmare</string>
<string name="110969"></string>
<string name="110970">Nightmare, saddle</string>
<string name="110971">Nightmare, barding</string>
<string name="110972">Horse, Jousting, Purple cloth</string>
<string name="110973">Horse, Jousting, Blue and gold cloth</string>
<string name="110974">Horse, Jousting, Black and white cloth</string>
<string name="110975">Horse, Jousting, Red and yellow cloth</string>
<string name="110976">Horse, Jousting, Red and black striped cloth</string>
<string name="110977">Horse, Jousting, Green cloth</string>
<string name="110978">Horse, Jousting, Blue and pink cloth</string>
<string name="110979">Horse, Jousting, Red and gold brick cloth</string>
<string name="110980">Horse, Jousting, Black cloth</string>
<string name="110981">Horse, Jousting, Cyan and white cloth</string>
<string name="110982">Horse, Jousting, White cloth</string>
<string name="110983">Curst Swordsman</string>
<string name="110984">Satyr, Archer</string>
<string name="110985">Satyr, Warrior</string>
<string name="110986">Ogre, Elite</string>
<string name="110987">Dragon, Mist</string>
<string name="110988">Satyr</string>
<string name="110989">Golem, Diamond</string>
<string name="110990">Golem, Emerald</string>
<string name="110991">Golem, Ruby</string>
<string name="110992">Snake, Black Cobra</string>
<string name="110993">Snake, Cobra</string>
<string name="110994">Snake, Gold Cobra</string>
<string name="110995">Beholder, G&apos;Zhorb</string>
<string name="110996">Purple Dragon Knight Archer, Female</string>
<string name="110997">Purple Dragon Knight Archer, Male</string>
<string name="110998">Purple Dragon Knight Blade, Female</string>
<string name="110999">Purple Dragon Knight Blade, Male</string>
<string name="111000">Lord Antoine</string>
<string name="111001">Caladnei</string>
<string name="111002">Wyvern, Adult</string>
<string name="111003">Wyvern, Great</string>
<string name="111004">Wyvern, Juvenile</string>
<string name="111005">Wyvern, Young</string>
<string name="111006">Hagatha</string>
<string name="111007">Halaster</string>
<string name="111008">Harat</string>
<string name="111009">Harat, Small</string>
<string name="111010">Maggris</string>
<string name="111011">Masterius</string>
<string name="111012">Masterius, Full Power</string>
<string name="111013">Witch King, Disguised</string>
<string name="111014">Wereboar</string>
<string name="111015">Normal mounted</string>
<string name="111016">Large mounted</string>
<string name="111017">Normal jousting mounted</string>
<string name="111018">Large jousting mounted</string>
<string name="111019">Rubble, Large</string>
<string name="111020">Map Dead End</string>
<string name="111021">Map Corner</string>
<string name="111022">Map T-junction</string>
<string name="111023">Map 4 way</string>
<string name="111024">Map Hall</string>
<string name="111025">Map Background</string>
<string name="111026">Icon Stairs Down</string>
<string name="111027">Icon Stairs Up</string>
<string name="111028">Icon Puzzle</string>
<string name="111029">Icon Battle</string>
<string name="111030">Icon Important</string>
<string name="111031">Icon Forge</string>
<string name="111032">Icon Camp</string>
<string name="111033">Torch 01</string>
<string name="111034">Table 01</string>
<string name="111035">Stand 01</string>
<string name="111036">Ambient Bird</string>
<string name="111037">Rowboat</string>
<string name="111038">Bush 01</string>
<string name="111039">Bush 02</string>
<string name="111040">Stocks, Prisoner</string>
<string name="111041">Stocks</string>
<string name="111042">Hay block 01</string>
<string name="111043">Barrel 01</string>
<string name="111044">Barrel 02</string>
<string name="111045">Barrel 03</string>
<string name="111046">Cloud, Ambient shadow</string>
<string name="111047">Market Stall 01</string>
<string name="111048">Hay block 02</string>
<string name="111049">Basket 01</string>
<string name="111050">Sign 01</string>
<string name="111051">Sign 02</string>
<string name="111052">Tree 01</string>
<string name="111053">Tree 02</string>
<string name="111054">Brazier</string>
<string name="111055">Torch 02</string>
<string name="111056">Tree, Apple, Large</string>
<string name="111057">Tree, Apple, Medium</string>
<string name="111058">Tree, Apple, Small</string>
<string name="111059">Tree, Birch A, Large</string>
<string name="111060">Tree, Birch A, Medium</string>
<string name="111061">Tree, Birch A, Small</string>
<string name="111062">Tree, Birch B, Large</string>
<string name="111063">Tree, Birch B, Medium</string>
<string name="111064">Tree, Birch B, Small</string>
<string name="111065">Tree, Birch C, Large</string>
<string name="111066">Tree, Birch C, Medium</string>
<string name="111067">Tree, Birch C, Small</string>
<string name="111068">Tree, Orange, Large</string>
<string name="111069">Tree, Orange, Medium</string>
<string name="111070">Tree, Orange, Small</string>
<string name="111071">Tree, Willow, Large</string>
<string name="111072">Tree, Willow, Medium</string>
<string name="111073">Tree, Willow, Small</string>
<string name="111074">Tree 0, Large</string>
<string name="111075">Tree 0, Medium</string>
<string name="111076">Tree 0, Small</string>
<string name="111077">Tree 1, Large</string>
<string name="111078">Tree 1, Medium</string>
<string name="111079">Tree 1, Small</string>
<string name="111080">Tree 2, Large</string>
<string name="111081">Tree 2, Medium</string>
<string name="111082">Tree 2, Small</string>
<string name="111083">Tree 3, Large</string>
<string name="111084">Tree 3, Medium</string>
<string name="111085">Tree 3, Small</string>
<string name="111086">Tree 4, Large</string>
<string name="111087">Tree 4, Medium</string>
<string name="111088">Tree 4, Small</string>
<string name="111089">Tree 5, Large</string>
<string name="111090">Tree 5, Medium</string>
<string name="111091">Tree 5, Small</string>
<string name="111092">Tree 6, Large</string>
<string name="111093">Tree 6, Medium</string>
<string name="111094">Tree 6, Small</string>
<string name="111095">Tree 7, Large</string>
<string name="111096">Tree 7, Medium</string>
<string name="111097">Tree 7, Small</string>
<string name="111098">Tree 8, Large</string>
<string name="111099">Tree 8, Medium</string>
<string name="111100">Tree 8, Small</string>
<string name="111101">Tree 9, Large</string>
<string name="111102">Tree 9, Medium</string>
<string name="111103">Tree 9, Small</string>
<string name="111104">Tree A, Large</string>
<string name="111105">Tree A, Medium</string>
<string name="111106">Tree A, Small</string>
<string name="111107">Tree B, Large</string>
<string name="111108">Tree B, Medium</string>
<string name="111109">Tree B, Small</string>
<string name="111110">Tree C, Large</string>
<string name="111111">Tree C, Medium</string>
<string name="111112">Tree C, Small</string>
<string name="111113">Balcony 1, Stone</string>
<string name="111114">Balcony 2, Wood</string>
<string name="111115">Balcony 3, Stone Railing</string>
<string name="111116">Balcony 4, Wood Railing</string>
<string name="111117">Balcony 5, Wood Large</string>
<string name="111118">Balcony 6, Wood Large Broken</string>
<string name="111119">Balcony 7, Stone Rounded Corners</string>
<string name="111120">Balcony 8, Wood Rounded Railing</string>
<string name="111121">Balcony 9, Stone Circlular</string>
<string name="111122">Balcony 10, Wood Circlular</string>
<string name="111123">Balcony 11, Wood Large Circlular</string>
<string name="111124">Balcony E1</string>
<string name="111125">Balcony E2</string>
<string name="111126">Balcony E3</string>
<string name="111127">Balcony E4</string>
<string name="111128">Chimney F1</string>
<string name="111129">Chimney F2</string>
<string name="111130">Balcony Door 1</string>
<string name="111131">Balcony Door 2</string>
<string name="111132">Window, Large Arch 1</string>
<string name="111133">Window, Large Arch 2 (High)</string>
<string name="111134">Window, Large Arch Interior</string>
<string name="111135">Window, Small Arch 1 (Low)</string>
<string name="111136">Window, Small Arch 2</string>
<string name="111137">Window, Small Arch 3 (High)</string>
<string name="111138">Window, Small Arch Interior</string>
<string name="111139">Window, Large 1</string>
<string name="111140">Window, Large 2 (High)</string>
<string name="111141">Window, Large Interior</string>
<string name="111142">Window, Small 1 (Low)</string>
<string name="111143">Window, Small 2</string>
<string name="111144">Window, Small 3 (High)</string>
<string name="111145">Window, Small Interior</string>
<string name="111146">Window, Arch Shuttered 1</string>
<string name="111147">Window, Arch Shuttered 2 (High)</string>
<string name="111148">Window, Arch Shuttered Interior</string>
<string name="111149">Scaffolding, Small</string>
<string name="111150">Scaffolding, Large</string>
<string name="111151">Bench A</string>
<string name="111152">Bench B</string>
<string name="111153">Pot, Giant</string>
<string name="111154">Shield Rack</string>
<string name="111155">Hanging Cage</string>
<string name="111156">Hangman&apos;s Scaffold</string>
<string name="111157">Log</string>
<string name="111158">Wagon</string>
<string name="111159">Dirt Patch 1</string>
<string name="111160">Dirt Patch 2</string>
<string name="111161">Dirt Patch 3</string>
<string name="111162">Gravel Patch</string>
<string name="111163">Grass Patch 1</string>
<string name="111164">Grass Patch 2</string>
<string name="111165">Grass Patch 3</string>
<string name="111166">Flag, Waukeen</string>
<string name="111167">Flag, Helm</string>
<string name="111168">Flag, Cyric</string>
<string name="111169">Flag, Torm</string>
<string name="111170">Flag, Sune</string>
<string name="111171">Flag, Bane</string>
<string name="111172">Flag, Lathander</string>
<string name="111173">Flag, Tempus</string>
<string name="111174">Flag, Mask</string>
<string name="111175">Flag, Eilistraee</string>
<string name="111176">Flag, Lolth</string>
<string name="111177">Flag, Ilmater</string>
<string name="111178">Flag, Waukeen, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111179">Flag, Helm, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111180">Flag, Cyric, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111181">Flag, Torm, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111182">Flag, Sune, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111183">Flag, Bane, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111184">Flag, Lathander, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111185">Flag, Tempus, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111186">Flag, Mask, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111187">Flag, Eilistraee, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111188">Flag, Lolth, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111189">Flag, Ilmater, Hanging at angle</string>
<string name="111190">Flag, Waukeen, Hanging</string>
<string name="111191">Flag, Helm, Hanging</string>
<string name="111192">Flag, Cyric, Hanging</string>
<string name="111193">Flag, Torm, Hanging</string>
<string name="111194">Flag, Sune, Hanging</string>
<string name="111195">Flag, Bane, Hanging</string>
<string name="111196">Flag, Lathander, Hanging</string>
<string name="111197">Flag, Tempus, Hanging</string>
<string name="111198">Flag, Mask, Hanging</string>
<string name="111199">Flag, Eilistraee, Hanging</string>
<string name="111200">Flag, Lolth, Hanging</string>
<string name="111201"></string>
<string name="111202">Flag, Ilmater, Hanging</string>
<string name="111203">Flag, Waukeen, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111204">Flag, Helm, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111205">Flag, Cyric, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111206">Flag, Torm, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111207">Flag, Sune, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111208">Flag, Bane, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111209">Flag, Lathander, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111210">Flag, Tempus, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111211">Flag, Mask, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111212">Flag, Eilistraee, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111213">Flag, Lolth, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111214">Flag, Ilmater, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111215">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield</string>
<string name="111216">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield 2</string>
<string name="111217">Flag, Raven and sword</string>
<string name="111218">Flag, Raven and crown</string>
<string name="111219">Flag, Joust, Green Stag 1</string>
<string name="111220">Flag, Joust, Green Stag 2</string>
<string name="111221">Flag, Joust, Raven and sword</string>
<string name="111222">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield</string>
<string name="111223">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield</string>
<string name="111224">Flag, Raven and sword</string>
<string name="111225">Flag, Raven and crown</string>
<string name="111226">Flag, Raven and Shield, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111227">Flag, Raven and sword, Hanging pennant 2</string>
<string name="111228">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant</string>
<string name="111229">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant 2</string>
<string name="111230">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant 3</string>
<string name="111231">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant 4</string>
<string name="111232">Flag, Raven and sword, Hanging pennant 3</string>
<string name="111233">Flag, Raven and Shield, Hanging pennant 4</string>
<string name="111234">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant 5</string>
<string name="111235">Flag, Green stag, Hanging pennant 6</string>
<string name="111236">Flag, Raven and sword, Hanging pennant 5</string>
<string name="111237">Flag, Raven and Shield, Hanging pennant 6</string>
<string name="111238">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield, Hanging</string>
<string name="111239">Flag, Green Stag &amp; Shield, Hanging 2</string>
<string name="111240">Flag, Raven and crown, Hanging</string>
<string name="111241">Flag, Raven and sword, Hanging</string>
<string name="111242">Altar, Evil</string>
<string name="111243">Statue, Cyric</string>
<string name="111244">Alchemist&apos;s Apparatus 1</string>
<string name="111245">Alchemist&apos;s Apparatus 2</string>
<string name="111246">Smoke, Evil</string>
<string name="111247">Crystal Ball 1</string>
<string name="111248">Banner 01</string>
<string name="111249">Banner 02</string>
<string name="111250">Torch,Wall</string>
<string name="111251">Pillar, Wood</string>
<string name="111252">Pillar, Wood Broken</string>
<string name="111253">Rubble Pile 01</string>
<string name="111254">Rubble Pile 02</string>
<string name="111255">Table, large</string>
<string name="111256">Table, overthrown</string>
<string name="111257">Bench</string>
<string name="111258">Bench, overthrown</string>
<string name="111259">Rubble Pile 03</string>
<string name="111260">Hitching Post</string>
<string name="111261">Sand Pile 01</string>
<string name="111262">Sand Pile 02</string>
<string name="111263">Sand Pile 03</string>
<string name="111264">Sand Pile 04</string>
<string name="111265">Sea Weed 01, Ground</string>
<string name="111266">Sea Weed 02, Ground</string>
<string name="111267">Sea Weed 03, Ground</string>
<string name="111268">Sea Weed 04, Ground</string>
<string name="111269">Weed 01, Wall Pink</string>
<string name="111270">Weed 02, Wall Pink</string>
<string name="111271">Weed 03, Wall Pink</string>
<string name="111272">Weed 04, Wall Pink</string>
<string name="111273">Weed 05, Wall Grey</string>
<string name="111274">Weed 06, Wall Grey</string>
<string name="111275">Weed 07, Wall Grey</string>
<string name="111276">Weed 08, Wall Grey</string>
<string name="111277">Weed 09, Wall Green</string>
<string name="111278">Weed 10, Wall Green</string>
<string name="111279">Weed 11, Wall Green</string>
<string name="111280">Weed 12, Wall Green</string>
<string name="111281">Skeleton Warrior, Dead</string>
<string name="111282">Skeleton Mage, Dead</string>
<string name="111283">Skeleton Warrior 2, Dead</string>
<string name="111284">Sarcophagus</string>
<string name="111285">Lightshaft, Yellow Small</string>
<string name="111286">Lightshaft, Yellow Medium</string>
<string name="111287">Lightshaft, Yellow Large</string>
<string name="111288">Boulder 1, Green standing</string>
<string name="111289">Boulder 2, Green laying flat</string>
<string name="111290">Boulder 3, Green leaning</string>
<string name="111291">Boulder 4, Green broken</string>
<string name="111292">Roots, Ceiling</string>
<string name="111293">Mushrooms, Red small group</string>
<string name="111294">Mushrooms, Red large group</string>
<string name="111295">Mushrooms, Brown small group</string>
<string name="111296">Mushrooms, Brown large group</string>
<string name="111297">Mushrooms, Brown circle</string>
<string name="111298">Mushrooms, Brown broken circle</string>
<string name="111299">Mushrooms, Grey small group</string>
<string name="111300">Mushrooms, Grey large group</string>
<string name="111301">Urn</string>
<string name="111302">Jars</string>
<string name="111303">Lance Rack, Animated</string>
<string name="111304">Lance Rack 2, Partially full</string>
<string name="111305">Lance Rack 3, Empty</string>
<string name="111306">Boulder, Green Secret Door </string>
<string name="111307">Flag, Joust 1, Yellow Bird</string>
<string name="111308">Flag, Joust 2</string>
<string name="111309">Flag, Joust 3</string>
<string name="111310">Banner, Huge Wall 1, Purple Dragon</string>
<string name="111311">Banner, Huge Wall 1, Yellow Bird</string>
<string name="111312">Banner, Medium Wall 2, Yellow Bird</string>
<string name="111313">Banner, Medium Wall 1, Purple Dragon</string>
<string name="111314">Roots, Ceiling, Blocks movement</string>
<string name="111315">Mist, Ground</string>
<string name="111316">Shaft of Water</string>
<string name="111317">Tree stump 1</string>
<string name="111318">Tree stump 2</string>
<string name="111319">Tree stump 3</string>
<string name="111320">Tree stump 4</string>
<string name="111321">Tree, Chopped Down</string>
<string name="111322">Ballista</string>
<string name="111323">Cheval de Frise</string>
<string name="111324">Dartboard</string>
<string name="111325">Archery Target</string>
<string name="111326">Fern 1</string>
<string name="111327">Fern 2</string>
<string name="111328">Fern 3</string>
<string name="111329">Fern 4</string>
<string name="111330">Fern 5</string>
<string name="111331">Moss 1</string>
<string name="111332">Moss 2</string>
<string name="111333">Moss 3</string>
<string name="111334">Moss 4</string>
<string name="111335">Moss 5</string>
<string name="111336">Chest, Decorative head</string>
<string name="111337">Pillar 1, Barrows</string>
<string name="111338">Pillar 2, Barrows</string>
<string name="111339">Pillar 3, Barrows</string>
<string name="111340">Pillar 4, Barrows</string>
<string name="111341">Invisible Wall (blocks movement, visible for easy placement until initial state is set to &quot;Deactivated&quot;).</string>
<string name="111342">Ballista, Arbalet</string>
<string name="111343">Pedestal, Evil</string>
<string name="111344">Gem, Diamond</string>
<string name="111345">Gem, Ruby</string>
<string name="111346">Gem, Sapphire</string>
<string name="111347">Gem, Emerald</string>
<string name="111348">Lightshaft, White</string>
<string name="111349">Lightshaft, Red</string>
<string name="111350">Lightshaft, Blue</string>
<string name="111351">Lightshaft, Green</string>
<string name="111352">List 1, Walkable</string>
<string name="111353">List 2, Walkable</string>
<string name="111354">List 3, Walkable</string>
<string name="111355">List 4, Walkable</string>
<string name="111356">List 1</string>
<string name="111357">List 2</string>
<string name="111358">List 3</string>
<string name="111359">List 4</string>
<string name="111360">Blade Barrier</string>
<string name="111361">Statue, Wyvern </string>
<string name="111362">Pedestal, Sword</string>
<string name="111363">Pot, Giant No fire</string>
<string name="111364">Flame, Large No Glow</string>
<string name="111365">Flame, Medium No Glow</string>
<string name="111366">Flame, Small No Glow</string>
<string name="111367">Rainbow</string>
<string name="111368">Black Cormyrian Cobra</string>
<string name="111369">These snakes are not common, but are found in the forests and marshes of Cormyr. They are dangerous when approached, and at times can be found in groups, though the reason for this is not known.</string>
<string name="111370">Gold Cormyrian Cobra</string>
<string name="111371">Related to the Black Cobra, these snakes are rare. They are found in damp places, surviving often where other creatures do not. They are dangerous when approached, and at times can be found in groups, though the reason for this is not known.</string>
<string name="111372">Great Cobra</string>
<string name="111373">Hybrid Cormyrian Cobra</string>
<string name="111374">These snakes are not common, but are found in the forests and marshes of Cormyr. They are dangerous when approached, and at times can be found in groups, though the reason for this is not known. This one seems to have mutated in some way.</string>
<string name="111375">Spitting Cobra</string>
<string name="111376">Spitting cobras can quirt a stream of venom several feet, aiming for the eyes of their prey. When approached without caution, these snakes can be dangerous.</string>
<string name="111377">Diamond Golem</string>
<string name="111378">These 10 foot golems are often carved in the likenesses of knights or warriors.</string>
<string name="111379">Emerald Golem</string>
<string name="111380">Emerald Golems have facets of dark green, often with sparks in their eyes. No matter how an Emerald Golem is carved, it will slowly transform to a female form. Like other gemstone golems, they are immune to most magic.</string>
<string name="111381">Ruby Golem</string>
<string name="111382">Ruby Golems are 9 feet tall, with facets ranging from bright red to almost black. They are softer than other gemstone golems, but highly resistant to magic.</string>
<string name="111383">Nightmares are proud and evil creatures with hearts as black as the dark abysses from which they come. They are wild and restless creatures, doing evil wherever they can.</string>
<string name="111384">Satyr Archer</string>
<string name="111385">Satyrs are hedonistic creatures that frolic in the wild places. They are keen on drink and drunkeness, but can make stealthy hunters too.</string>
<string name="111386">Satyr Warrior</string>
<string name="111387">Great Wyvern</string>
<string name="111388">Larger than an ogre, these great lizards are distant cousins of dragons. Though capable of draconic speech, they have low intelligence and are aggressive in nature. Wyverns are common still over Lake Wyvernwater.</string>
<string name="111389">Adult Wyvern</string>
<string name="111390">Juvenile Wyvern</string>
<string name="111391">Young Wyvern</string>
<string name="111392">Whatever their form, wereboars fight with the ferocity of a cornered wild boar. These lycanthropes are tenacious and difficult to bring down.</string>
<string name="111393">Mist Dragon</string>
<string name="111394">Mist dragons are normally solitary and philosophical. Their favorite activity is sitting quietly and thinking. They hate being disturbed and they dislike conversation.</string>
<string name="111395">Purple Dragon Archer</string>
<string name="111396">A &apos;blade&apos; of the Purple Dragons, the regular soldiers of Cormyr. These men and women are tough and experienced after the recent war with the ghazneths that rolled across Cormyr.</string>
<string name="111397">Purple Dragon Blade</string>
<string name="111398">The heart of a shattered Gem Golem, a flawless ruby.</string>
<string name="111399">Ruby Golem Heart</string>
<string name="111400">Diamond Golem Heart</string>
<string name="111401">The heart of a shattered Gem Golem, a flawless diamond.</string>
<string name="111402">Emerald Golem Heart</string>
<string name="111403">The heart of a shattered Gem Golem, a flawless emerald.</string>
<string name="111404">Diamond Greatsword</string>
<string name="111405">Diamond Golem Properties</string>
<string name="111406">Diamond Golem Fist</string>
<string name="111407">Emerald Golem Properties</string>
<string name="111408">Emerald Warhammer</string>
<string name="111409">Emerald Shield</string>
<string name="111410">Ruby Golem Properties</string>
<string name="111411">Ruby Warhammer</string>
<string name="111412">Ruby Shield</string>
<string name="111413">Wyvern Blood</string>
<string name="111414">Wyvern Tail</string>
<string name="111415">Wyvern blood, used for making inks, and occasionally for tempering metals.</string>
<string name="111416">Snake Properties</string>
<string name="111417">Nightmare Hoof</string>
<string name="111418">Cobra Bite 1d4</string>
<string name="111419">Cobra Bite 1d6</string>
<string name="111420">Cobra Bite 1d10</string>
<string name="111421">Cold Iron Blade</string>
<string name="111422">Since the war with the Devil Dragon, these blades are fairly common in Cormyr. They were manufactured in large numbers to equip the Purple Dragons, for it was only with Cold Iron that the ghazneths could be harmed.</string>
<string name="111423">Purple Dragon Shield</string>
<string name="111424">A shield from a soldier of Cormyr, a Purple Dragon.

This item is considered stolen if you take it.</string>
<string name="111425">Purple Dragon Helmet</string>
<string name="111426">A helmet usually worn by heavily armored soldiers of the Purple Dragons.</string>
<string name="111427">Purple Dragon Mail</string>
<string name="111428">A suit of scale mail belonging to the Purple Dragons.</string>
<string name="111429">Purple Dragon Light Armor</string>
<string name="111430">Light armor belonging to the Purple Dragons.</string>
<string name="111431">Curst Swordsman</string>
<string name="111432">Black Mail</string>
<string name="111433">This mail shirt is made from a dark alloy of metal but otherwise is unremarkable.</string>
<string name="111434">These chain shirts were commonly worn by reavers in the early days of Cormyr. Dressed in their black mail shirts, the reavers silently attacked farming families, stealing not only their goods, but their women too, unless the farmers paid them off. The terms &apos;blackmail&apos; and &apos;bereaved&apos; soon became commonplace.</string>
<string name="111435">G&apos;Zhorb, the All-Seeing Eye</string>
<string name="111436">This old, scarred beholder looks like he has faced down armies and laughed about it.</string>
<string name="111437">Lord Antoine Baccha, Visier de Guise</string>
<string name="111438">This boorish noble seems to be both eccentric and ferocious at the same time.</string>
<string name="111439">Widow Hagatha</string>
<string name="111440">This cloud giant is so old and withered that it is surprising she could possibly be alive, let alone command so much power.</string>
<string name="111441">Halaster</string>
<string name="111442">Halaster is the master of Undermountain. He is reputed to be mad and very powerful.</string>
<string name="111443">Ring of Regeneration</string>
<string name="111444">Halaster Properties</string>
<string name="111445">Horned Ring</string>
<string name="111446">This item belongs to Halaster Blackcloak. He carries it at all times.</string>
<string name="111447">Robe of Eyes</string>
<string name="111448">Maggris, the Hive Mother</string>
<string name="111449">The insect-like creature in front of you moves with a delicate step and a deliberate intelligence.</string>
<string name="111450">Bite 4d6 + 12</string>
<string name="111451">Masterius, the Lich King</string>
<string name="111452">Old and powerful, as any lich is bound to be, there is a palpable aura of energy surrounding the Lich King.</string>
<string name="111453">Dwarf rider</string>
<string name="111454">Elf rider</string>
<string name="111455">Human rider</string>
<string name="111456">Horse</string>
<string name="111457">Horses make useful beasts of burden, and the best of them also make good warhorses.</string>
<string name="111458">Heavy War Horse</string>
<string name="111459">Jousting Horse</string>
<string name="111460">Caladnei</string>
<string name="111461">Caladnei, the Royal Wizard, and the foremost sorceress of Cormyr. Tutored by Vangerdahast, she is a fine ally, or a formidable foe.</string>
<string name="111462">Harat, Lord of Darkness</string>
<string name="111463">This demon is surrounded by a dark malevolence that could drive a person mad if they stared too long.</string>
<string name="111464">Harat Properties</string>
<string name="111465">Exterior, Muggy</string>
<string name="111466">Interior, Barrows</string>
<string name="111467">Barrows Interior</string>
<string name="111468">City Interior 2</string>
<string name="111469">Castle Interior 2</string>
<string name="111470">Castle Exterior, Rural</string>
<string name="111471">Steamworks</string>
<string name="111472">Fort Interior</string>
<string name="111473">Wall Section 1</string>
<string name="111474">Wall Section 2</string>
<string name="111475">Platform 1 1x1 </string>
<string name="111476">Platform 2 1x1 </string>
<string name="111477">Platform 3 1x1 </string>
<string name="111478">Side Chamber 1</string>
<string name="111479">Secret Passage</string>
<string name="111480">Stone Formation 1</string>
<string name="111481">Stone Formation 2</string>
<string name="111482">Exit Down 2x1</string>
<string name="111483">Corridor Down 1x2</string>
<string name="111484">Corridor Up 1 1x2 </string>
<string name="111485">Final Area 7x7 (turn off tile property &quot;Animation Loop 1&quot; to remove the white pillar location textures)</string>
<string name="111486">Corridor Up 2 1x2 </string>
<string name="111487">Barrow</string>
<string name="111488">Doorway Barrow</string>
<string name="111489">Doorway Corridor</string>
<string name="111490">Round Room 1x1 Up &amp; Down</string>
<string name="111491">Round Room 1x1 Up</string>
<string name="111492">Round Room 1x1 Down</string>
<string name="111493">Smithy 2x2</string>
<string name="111494">House / Shop 2x2</string>
<string name="111495">Ship Cabin 1x2</string>
<string name="111496">Tent Blue/White 1x1</string>
<string name="111497">Tent Blue/White 2x2</string>
<string name="111498">Tent Blue/White 5x3</string>
<string name="111499">Tent Red/Black 1x1</string>
<string name="111500">Tent Red/Black 2x2</string>
<string name="111501">Tent Red/Black 5x3</string>
<string name="111502">Tent Red/White 1x1</string>
<string name="111503">Tent Red/White 2x2</string>
<string name="111504">Tent Red/White 5x3</string>
<string name="111505">Round 2x2 Down</string>
<string name="111506">Round 2x2 Up &amp; Down</string>
<string name="111507">Round 2x2 Up</string>
<string name="111508">Round Basement 1x1 Up &amp; Down</string>
<string name="111509">Round Basement 1x1 Up</string>
<string name="111510">Round Basement 1x1 Down</string>
<string name="111511">Round Basement 1x1</string>
<string name="111512">Basement 1x2</string>
<string name="111513">Collapsed Room 2x2</string>
<string name="111514">Mythallar 3x3</string>
<string name="111515">Round Tower 2x2</string>
<string name="111516">Sea Cliffs</string>
<string name="111517">Castle Crosser</string>
<string name="111518">Sea Cliffs Sand Crosser</string>
<string name="111519">Low Wall</string>
<string name="111520">Castle High</string>
<string name="111521">Joust Lists</string>
<string name="111522">Joust Lists Small</string>
<string name="111523">Grass Raise/Lower</string>
<string name="111524">Grassy Trees</string>
<string name="111525">Lake/Moat</string>
<string name="111526">Ridge</string>
<string name="111527">Castle Low</string>
<string name="111528">Tent, Small 1</string>
<string name="111529">Tent, Small 2</string>
<string name="111530">Range</string>
<string name="111531">Fisherman 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111532">Fisherman 2 1x1</string>
<string name="111533">Ice Cellar</string>
<string name="111534">Well</string>
<string name="111535">Tower, Circular Path 3x3</string>
<string name="111536">Tower 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111537">Stone Circle 2x2</string>
<string name="111538">Stone Dolman</string>
<string name="111539">Castle Tower 3x3</string>
<string name="111540">Tent, Small 3</string>
<string name="111541">Mill 2x2</string>
<string name="111542">House, L-Shape 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111543">House 1x3</string>
<string name="111544">Market Stall 02</string>
<string name="111545">Market Stall 03</string>
<string name="111546">House 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111547">House Tower 5</string>
<string name="111548">Inn 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111549">House, Arcaded 2x2</string>
<string name="111550">Tent, Medium 1</string>
<string name="111551">Stores 1x2</string>
<string name="111552">House Tower 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111553">Tower 2 2x2</string>
<string name="111554">Inn, Coach 2x2</string>
<string name="111555">Market 2x2</string>
<string name="111556">Watchtower</string>
<string name="111557">Roundhouse 1x1</string>
<string name="111558">House 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111559">Tent, Medium 2</string>
<string name="111560">Roundhouse, Small</string>
<string name="111561">House 2 1x1</string>
<string name="111562">House 3 1x1</string>
<string name="111563">House Tower 2 1x1</string>
<string name="111564">House 4 1x1</string>
<string name="111565">House 5 1x1</string>
<string name="111566">House Tower 6 1x1</string>
<string name="111567">House 6 1x1</string>
<string name="111568">House 7 1x1</string>
<string name="111569">House Tower 3 1x1</string>
<string name="111570">Tent, Medium 3</string>
<string name="111571">House Tower 4 1x1</string>
<string name="111572">House 1x2</string>
<string name="111573">Simple Stage</string>
<string name="111574">Forge  2x2</string>
<string name="111575">Stables, Grass</string>
<string name="111576">Fantasy Tower 4x4</string>
<string name="111577">Tent, Large 1</string>
<string name="111578">Graves 6</string>
<string name="111579">Field 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111580">Field 2 1x2</string>
<string name="111581">Tent, Large 2</string>
<string name="111582">Castle High Gate</string>
<string name="111583">Ship 4x1</string>
<string name="111584">Boat, Anchored</string>
<string name="111585">Water Road - Gate</string>
<string name="111586">Low Wall, Gate Wood</string>
<string name="111587">Low Wall, Gate Iron</string>
<string name="111588">Castle Crosser, Passage</string>
<string name="111589">Castle Crosser, Stairs</string>
<string name="111590">Tent, Large 3</string>
<string name="111591">Ship 3x1</string>
<string name="111592">Burned House 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111593">Burned House 2 1x1</string>
<string name="111594">Burned House 2x1</string>
<string name="111595">Hay Barn</string>
<string name="111596">Joust Stands 1 1x3</string>
<string name="111597">Joust Stands 1x2</string>
<string name="111598">Burned House 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111599">Burned House 2 2x2</string>
<string name="111600">Barrows Entry 2x2</string>
<string name="111601">Stone Circle Portal 1x1</string>
<string name="111602">Joust Stands 2 1x3</string>
<string name="111603">House L-Shape 2 2x2</string>
<string name="111604">House L-Shape 1 2x2</string>
<string name="111605">House Tower 5 1x1</string>
<string name="111606">Stables 1x2</string>
<string name="111607">Market, Rich 2x2</string>
<string name="111608">Graves 7</string>
<string name="111609">Chapel 3x2</string>
<string name="111610">Mausoleum 2x2</string>
<string name="111611">Fountain 1x1</string>
<string name="111612">Inn 2 2x2</string>
<string name="111613">Docks 1x2</string>
<string name="111614">Docked Ship 2x4</string>
<string name="111615">Boat, Docked 2x2</string>
<string name="111616">Sewer Entrance 1x2</string>
<string name="111617">Ship Docked 3x2</string>
<string name="111618">Forge 2x2</string>
<string name="111619">Path Down</string>
<string name="111620">Cave Entrance 1x2</string>
<string name="111621">Cliff Road, Gate</string>
<string name="111622">Stairs Down, Cliff 1x1</string>
<string name="111623">Cog 3x1</string>
<string name="111624">Cog Anchored 3x1</string>
<string name="111625">Wall Cave 1x2</string>
<string name="111626">Drawbridge (passage walkable) 1x2</string>
<string name="111627">Cave Entrance 1x1</string>
<string name="111628">Drawbridge 1x2</string>
<string name="111629">Path Down 3x3</string>
<string name="111630">Boat, Landed</string>
<string name="111631">Ship 4x1 , Anchored</string>
<string name="111632">Inner Wall, Stairs 1x1</string>
<string name="111633">Castle Wall, Gate 1x2</string>
<string name="111634">Outer Wall, Gate 1x1</string>
<string name="111635">Keep, StairsTop</string>
<string name="111636">Outer Wall 1, Door</string>
<string name="111637">Outer Wall 2, Door</string>
<string name="111638">Large Door 1x1</string>
<string name="111639">Storage, Corridor 1x1</string>
<string name="111640">Room, Generic 1x1</string>
<string name="111641">Exit Down 1x1</string>
<string name="111642">Exit, Collapsed Wall 1x1</string>
<string name="111643">Doorway, Spiral Stair Down 1x1</string>
<string name="111644">Doorway, Spiral Stair Up 1x1</string>
<string name="111645">Doorway, Spiral Stair Up &amp; Down 1x1</string>
<string name="111646">Corridor Stairs Up &amp; Down 1x1</string>
<string name="111647">Bedroom 1 1x1</string>
<string name="111648">Library 1x1</string>
<string name="111649">Cells 1x1</string>
<string name="111650">Arena 1x2</string>
<string name="111651">Dais 1x2</string>
<string name="111652">Store Room, L-Shape 2x2</string>
<string name="111653">Cells 2x2</string>
<string name="111654">Large Gate 1x2</string>
<string name="111655">Room, Generic 2x1</string>
<string name="111656">Room, Generic 2x2</string>
<string name="111657">Large Gate Exit 1x2</string>
<string name="111658">Platform 1x2</string>
<string name="111659">Kitchen 1x2</string>
<string name="111660">Bedroom 3 1x2</string>
<string name="111661">Portal Hall 2x3</string>
<string name="111662">Arch / Wall Crosser</string>
<string name="111663">Building Adornments</string>
<string name="111664">Tree Stump</string>
<string name="111665">Stand</string>
<string name="111666">Bird</string>
<string name="111667">Bush</string>
<string name="111668">Basket</string>
<string name="111669">Balcony</string>
<string name="111670">Chimney</string>
<string name="111671">Balcony Door</string>
<string name="111672">Scaffolding</string>
<string name="111673">Giant Pot</string>
<string name="111674">DM Tool 1</string>
<string name="111675">DM Tool 2</string>
<string name="111676">DM Tool 3</string>
<string name="111677">DM Tool 4</string>
<string name="111678">DM Tool 5</string>
<string name="111679">DM Tool 6</string>
<string name="111680">DM Tool 7</string>
<string name="111681">DM Tool 8</string>
<string name="111682">DM Tool 9</string>
<string name="111683">DM Tool 10</string>
<string name="111684">Player Tool 1</string>
<string name="111685">Player Tool 2</string>
<string name="111686">Player Tool 3</string>
<string name="111687">Player Tool 4</string>
<string name="111688">Player Tool 5</string>
<string name="111689">Player Tool 6</string>
<string name="111690">Player Tool 7</string>
<string name="111691">Player Tool 8</string>
<string name="111692">Player Tool 9</string>
<string name="111693">Player Tool 10</string>
<string name="111694">A large, solid piece of granite lies on the ground.</string>
<string name="111695">A large piece of granite lies broken on the ground.</string>
<string name="111696">Mist</string>
<string name="111697">Lance</string>
<string name="111698">Trumpet</string>
<string name="111699">Tourney Lances used for jousting are made of light, easily broken wood and designed to widen outwards to protect the wielder from splinters and shards. The head is made of wood or a weak metal, and is designed with a broad tip to lessen the force of impact, which decrease the chances of injury.</string>
<string name="111700">Usually made of brass, the trumpet is a musical instrument that has seen many incarnations. It is often favored for pomp and pageantry, its players important heralds or messengers in royal courts. Trumpet players are often among the most heavily guarded members of a troop, as they are relied upon to relay instructions to other sections of the army.</string>
<string name="111701">Moon-on-a-Stick</string>
<string name="111702">The item attached to the end of this long thin piece of wood resembles the Moon. Now you have everything you&apos;ve ever wanted.</string>
<string name="111703">Base Damage: 1d0 
Base Critical Threat: x1 
Base Damage Type: Bludgeoning 
Weapon Size: Small 
Feats Required: None</string>
<string name="111704">Base Damage: 1d2 
Base Critical Threat: x1
Base Damage Type: Bludgeoning
Weapon Size: Small 
Feats Required: 
Base Item: Trumpet 
Weight: 0.5</string>
<string name="111705"></string>
<string name="111706"></string>
<string name="111707">Gem Golem</string>
<string name="111708">Snake</string>
<string name="111709">Mechanical</string>
<string name="111710">Purple Dragon Knight</string>
<string name="111711">Purple Dragon Knights</string>
<string name="111712">purple dragon knight</string>
<string name="111713">(PRESTIGE CLASS)
The famous Purple Dragons of Cormyr are regarded across Faerun as exemplars of disciplined, skilled, loyal soldiers. Their reputation is deserved partly because of the heroic actions of their leaders, the Purple Dragon Knights. Purple Dragon Knights develop uncanny skills relating to coordinating and leading soldiers. Most are fighters, rangers or paladins, but a few bards, clerics, and rogues have been known to become Purple Dragon Knights. Sorcerers and Wizards tend to join the War Wizards, Cormyr&apos;s elite brigade of fighting spellcasters, while barbarians are too undisciplined, and druids and monks too &quot;uncivilized&quot; in Cormyr to enter this career.

- Hit Die: d10.
- Proficiencies: A purple dragon knight gains no additional proficiences.
- Skill Points: 2 + Int Modifier.

REQUIREMENTS:

Alignment: Non-Evil and Non-Chaotic.
Base Attack Bonus: +4.
Feats: Mounted Combat (requires Ride 1).
Skills: Spot 2 ranks, Intimidate 1 rank, Listen 2 ranks, Persuade 1 rank, Ride 2 ranks.

ABILITIES:

Level
1: Rallying Cry - +1 Attack Bonus to all allies within 60 feet, can be used three times a day.
    Heroic Shield - Able to defend a nearby ally, granting them a +4 armor class bonus for one round.
2: Inspire Courage - +2 saves vs. mind affecting, and +1 attack and damage, useable once a day.
3: Fear - As fear spell, useable once per day.
4: Inspire Courage - Can now be used twice a day.
   Oath of Wrath - +2 bonus to attack, damage, saves and skill vs. single enemy.
5: Final Stand - +2d10 HP to a number of allies equal to Purple Dragon Knight level + Charisma Bonus, once per day.</string>
<string name="111714">Rallying Cry</string>
<string name="111715">Type of Feat: Class.
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 1.
Specifics: Three times per day, a Purple Dragon Knight can utter a powerful shout that gives all allies a +1 bonus to attack and a 20% bonus to land speed for one round.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111716">Heroic Shield</string>
<string name="111717">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 1.
Specifics: You may aid an ally, giving them a +4 bonus to their armour class for one round.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111718">Fear</string>
<string name="111719">Type of Feat: Class.
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 3.
Specifics: Once per day, the Purple Dragon Knight may cast the Fear spell with a caster level equal to his character level.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111720">Oath of Wrath</string>
<string name="111721">Type of Feat: Class.
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 4.
Specifics: Once per day, the Purple Dragon Knight may swear to defeat a single opponent. He gains a +2 bonus to Attack, Damage, Saves, and Skills vs that opponent. This lasts for a number of rounds equal to twice his class level.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111722">Final Stand</string>
<string name="111723">Type of Feat: Class.
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 5.
Specifics: Once per day, the Purple Dragon Knight can inspire his troops to a heroic effort. Each ally in the area gains 2d10 hitpoints. This ability can affect a number of people equal to his Purple Dragon Knight level + Charisma modifier, and lasts for the same number of rounds.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111724">Inspire Courage</string>
<string name="111725">Type of Feat: Class.
Prerequisite: Purple Dragon Knight level 2.
Specifics: Once per day, the Purple Dragon Knight can inspire his troops in combat. All affected creatures gain a +1 bonus to Attack and Damage, and a +2 bonus against mind affecting spells. These bonuses last for 10 rounds.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111726">Ride</string>
<string name="111727">Ability: Dexterity.
Requires Training: No.
Classes: All.

The character has spent time training to use a horse in combat, and can perform actions unskilled people cannot.</string>
<string name="111728">Mounted Combat</string>
<string name="111729">Type of Feat: General.
Prerequisite: Ride 1 rank.
Required for: Mounted Archery
Specifics: While mounted, once per round you will attempt a Ride check to increase your Armour Class by 1 point for every 5 of the check result.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="111730">Mounted Archery</string>
<string name="111731">Type of Feat: General.
Prerequisite: Ride 1 rank, Mounted Combat.
Specifics: The attack penalty for using a bow while mounted is reduced from -4 to -2.
Use: Automatic.</string>
<string name="111732">-11</string>
<string name="111733">-12</string>
<string name="111734">-13</string>
<string name="111735">-14</string>
<string name="111736">-15</string>
<string name="111737">-16</string>
<string name="111738">-17</string>
<string name="111739">-18</string>
<string name="111740">-19</string>
<string name="111741">-20</string>
<string name="111742">-21</string>
<string name="111743">-22</string>
<string name="111744">-23</string>
<string name="111745">-24</string>
<string name="111746">-25</string>
<string name="111747">-26</string>
<string name="111748">-27</string>
<string name="111749">-28</string>
<string name="111750">-29</string>
<string name="111751">-30</string>
<string name="111752">-31</string>
<string name="111753">-32</string>
<string name="111754">-33</string>
<string name="111755">-34</string>
<string name="111756">-35</string>
<string name="111757">-36</string>
<string name="111758">-37</string>
<string name="111759">-38</string>
<string name="111760">-39</string>
<string name="111761">-40</string>
<string name="111762">-41</string>
<string name="111763">-42</string>
<string name="111764">-43</string>
<string name="111765">-44</string>
<string name="111766">-45</string>
<string name="111767">-46</string>
<string name="111768">-47</string>
<string name="111769">-48</string>
<string name="111770">-49</string>
<string name="111771">-50</string>
<string name="111772">Material</string>
<string name="111773">Material:</string>
<string name="111774">Materials are substances that are used to compose an item.  Materials, and the understanding of the use of them, form the basis of civilization.

Some materials must be refined from other raw materials.  Others have innate magical properties and are sought after by many.

When it comes to complex weapons and armor, the right materials can spell the difference between life or death.
</string>
<string name="111775">Unknown</string>
<string name="111776">Adamantine</string>
<string name="111777">Brass</string>
<string name="111778">Bronze</string>
<string name="111779">Carbon</string>
<string name="111780">Cold Iron</string>
<string name="111781">Copper</string>
<string name="111782">Darksteel</string>
<string name="111783">Gold</string>
<string name="111784">Iron</string>
<string name="111785">Lead</string>
<string name="111786">Mithral</string>
<string name="111787">Platinum</string>
<string name="111788">Silver</string>
<string name="111789">Silver, Alchemical</string>
<string name="111790">Steel</string>
<string name="111791">Bone</string>
<string name="111792">Hide</string>
<string name="111793">Hide, Salamander</string>
<string name="111794">Hide, Umber Hulk</string>
<string name="111795">Hide, Wyvern</string>
<string name="111796">Hide, Dragon, Black</string>
<string name="111797">Hide, Dragon, Blue</string>
<string name="111798">Hide, Dragon, Brass</string>
<string name="111799">Hide, Dragon, Bronze</string>
<string name="111800">Hide, Dragon, Copper</string>
<string name="111801">Hide, Dragon, Gold</string>
<string name="111802">Hide, Dragon, Green</string>
<string name="111803">Hide, Dragon, Red</string>
<string name="111804">Hide, Dragon, Silver</string>
<string name="111805">Hide, Dragon, White</string>
<string name="111806">Leather</string>
<string name="111807">Scale</string>
<string name="111808">Cloth</string>
<string name="111809">Cotton</string>
<string name="111810">Silk</string>
<string name="111811">Wool</string>
<string name="111812">Wood</string>
<string name="111813">Wood, Ironwood</string>
<string name="111814">Wood, Duskwood</string>
<string name="111815">Wood, Darkwood, Zalantar</string>
<string name="111816">Wood, Ash</string>
<string name="111817">Wood, Yew</string>
<string name="111818">Wood, Oak</string>
<string name="111819">Wood, Pine</string>
<string name="111820">Wood, Cedar</string>
<string name="111821">Elemental</string>
<string name="111822">Elemental, Air</string>
<string name="111823">Elemental, Earth</string>
<string name="111824">Elemental, Fire</string>
<string name="111825">Elemental, Water</string>
<string name="111826">Gem</string>
<string name="111827">Gem, Alexandrite</string>
<string name="111828">Gem, Amethyst</string>
<string name="111829">Gem, Aventurine</string>
<string name="111830">Gem, Beljuril</string>
<string name="111831">Gem, Bloodstone</string>
<string name="111832">Gem, Blue Diamond</string>
<string name="111833">Gem, Canary Diamond</string>
<string name="111834">Gem, Diamond</string>
<string name="111835">Gem, Emerald</string>
<string name="111836">Gem, Fire Agate</string>
<string name="111837">Gem, Fire Opal</string>
<string name="111838">Gem, Flourspar</string>
<string name="111839">Gem, Garnet</string>
<string name="111840">Gem, Greenstone</string>
<string name="111841">Gem, Jacinth</string>
<string name="111842">Gem, Kings Tear</string>
<string name="111843">Gem, Malachite</string>
<string name="111844">Gem, Obsidian</string>
<string name="111845">Gem, Phenalope</string>
<string name="111846">Gem, Rogue Stone</string>
<string name="111847">Gem, Ruby</string>
<string name="111848">Gem, Sapphire</string>
<string name="111849">Gem, Star Sapphire</string>
<string name="111850">Gem, Topaz</string>
<string name="111851">Gem, Crystal, Deep</string>
<string name="111852">Gem, Crystal, Mundane</string>
<string name="111853">Quality</string>
<string name="111854">Quality:</string>
<string name="111855">No two tools are alike. Quality of workmanship and material increase the perfomance and longevity of an item. The time put in to manufacturing a quality product is returned ten-fold thereafter.</string>
<string name="111856">Destroyed</string>
<string name="111857">Ruined</string>
<string name="111858">Very Poor</string>
<string name="111859">Poor</string>
<string name="111860">Below Average</string>
<string name="111861">Average</string>
<string name="111862">Above Average</string>
<string name="111863">Good</string>
<string name="111864">Very Good</string>
<string name="111865">Excellent</string>
<string name="111866">Masterwork</string>
<string name="111867">Godlike</string>
<string name="111868">Raw</string>
<string name="111869">Cut</string>
<string name="111870">Polished</string>
<string name="111871">Additional Property</string>
<string name="111872">Additional Property:</string>
<string name="111873">This is an unknown property.</string>
<string name="111874">Cursed</string>
<string name="111875">Mount Actions</string>
<string name="111876">Type of Feat: General
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This series of actions enables players to interact with their mounts.
Use: Selected.

Individual Mount: Ride on the targetted mount, or command the targetted henchman to ride on a mount.
Individual Dismount: Targetted creature dismounts.</string>
<string name="111877">Individual Mount</string>
<string name="111878">Type of Feat: General
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: Use this feat on a horse that is in your party to mount it. Use this feat on a henchman to instruct him or her to mount the first available horse in the party.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111879">Individual Dismount</string>
<string name="111880">Type of Feat: General
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: Use this feat to dismount. Use this feat on a mounted henchman to instruct him or her to dismount.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111881">Summon Mount</string>
<string name="111882">Type of Feat: Class
Prerequisite: Paladin
Specifics: Summons to the paladin a faithful, magical beast - a warhorse mount. The beast is more powerful as the paladin gets more powerful.

Note: Horses and the Ride skill are only used in the Premium Module &quot;Neverwinter Nights - Wyvern Crown of Cormyr&quot; and specific community made modules.

Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111883">Party Mount</string>
<string name="111884">Specifics: In parties with several members and mounts, this feat commands all members to mount up all at once.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111885">Party Dismount</string>
<string name="111886">Specifics: In parties with several members and mounts, this feat commands all members to dismount all at once.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111887">Assign Mount</string>
<string name="111888">Specifics: Assign a mount to a particular companion, so he will always ride on the same mount.
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111889">Ride</string>
<string name="111890">Ability: Dexterity.
Requires Training: No.
Classes: All.

The character has spent time training to use a horse in combat, and can perform actions unskilled people cannot.

Note: Horses and the Ride skill are only used in the Premium Module &quot;Neverwinter Nights - Wyvern Crown of Cormyr&quot; and specific community made modules.</string>
<string name="111891">Nightmare, Smoke</string>
<string name="111892">In the excitement of combat, the Nightmare snorts and neighs with rage. This fills the surrounding area with hot sulfurous smoke that conceals the Nightmare.</string>
<string name="111893">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt; rally cries.</string>
<string name="111894">Trident +1</string>
<string name="111895">Trident +2</string>
<string name="111896">Trident +3</string>
<string name="111897">Trident +4</string>
<string name="111898">Trident +5</string>
<string name="111899">Trident +6</string>
<string name="111900">Trident +7</string>
<string name="111901">Trident +8</string>
<string name="111902">Trident of Thunder</string>
<string name="111903">PM - Infinite Dungeons</string>
<string name="111904">PM - Wyvern Crown Armchair</string>
<string name="111905">PM - Wyvern Crown Knighted</string>
<string name="111906">PM - Wyvern Crown Ogma</string>
<string name="111907">PM - Wyvern Crown Battle</string>
<string name="111908">PM - Wyvern Crown Battle Chase</string>
<string name="111909">PM - Wyvern Crown Morfen</string>
<string name="111910">PM - Wyvern Crown Opening</string>
<string name="111911">PM - Wyvern Crown Open Road</string>
<string name="111912">PM - Wyvern Crown Rural</string>
<string name="111913">PM - Wyvern Crown Rural Guitar</string>
<string name="111914">PM - Wyvern Crown Smoke and Ash</string>
<string name="111915">PM - Wyvern Crown Solace</string>
<string name="111916">PM - Wyvern Crown Tears</string>
<string name="111917">PM - Wyvern Crown Theme</string>
<string name="111918">Boulder</string>
<string name="111919">Cloth</string>
<string name="111920">Spiked Green Stone Door</string>
<string name="111921">Spiked Brown Stone Door</string>
<string name="111922">Wood Door</string>
<string name="111923">Metal Jail Door</string>
<string name="111924">Wood Jail Door</string>
<string name="111925">Stone Interlocking Door</string>
<string name="111926">Metal Interlocking Door</string>
<string name="111927">Steamworks Door</string>
<string name="111928">Strong Metal Door</string>
<string name="111929">Evil Metal Door</string>
<string name="111930">Area Transition (No Visible Door)</string>
<string name="111931">Special</string>
<string name="111932">Market 2x2</string>
<string name="111933">Default Purple Dragon Knight</string>
<string name="111934">The standard Purple Dragon Knight is trained in coordinating and leading soldiers which includes the use of the longsword and combat-oriented feats.

These packages do not give any special abilities to your character, they simply configure your skills and feats so you don&apos;t have to.</string>
<string name="111935">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool01 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111936">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool02 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111937">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool03 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111938">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool04 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111939">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool05 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111940">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool06 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111941">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool07 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111942">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool08 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111943">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool09 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111944">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: All DM characters start with this Instant feat. This feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_dm_tool10 script in the toolset. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111945">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool01 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111946">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool02 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111947">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool03 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111948">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool04 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111949">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool05 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111950">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool06 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111951">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool07 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111952">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool08 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111953">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool09 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111954">Type of Feat: Instant Custom
Prerequisite: None
Specifics: This instant feat can be given to players to enable a behavior you desire. The feat does nothing unless implemented in a community made module. The feat is implemented by editing the x3_pl_tool10 script in the toolset and then giving the feat to a player. This can be done by adding a item property bonus feat to a creature skin that has been previously equipped by the player through scripting. 
Use: Selected.</string>
<string name="111955">Portable Encampment</string>
<string name="111956">There are many dangers lurking, and unwary travelers can find themselves accosted or even killed by resting in unsecured surroundings. By using a Portable Encampment (tm) by AdventureCo, they can rest easy in the peace and security provided by an encampment designed and built by the lowest bidder.</string>
<string name="111957">You cannot use this item in combat.</string>
<string name="111958">A large mound of rubble is heaped on the ground.</string>
<string name="111959">** Summon and Mount Paladin Horse Failed! **</string>
<string name="111960">That is not permitted in this area.</string>
<string name="111961">That henchman is already mounted!</string>
<string name="111962">That henchman does not have a horse assigned to it or otherwise cannot mount!</string>
<string name="111963">You cannot order that target to dismount.</string>
<string name="111964">That target is not mounted.</string>
<string name="111965">That target cannot be dismounted.</string>
<string name="111966">To use Assign Mount, the targets involved must be dismounted.</string>
<string name="111967">Paladin Mounts may not be assigned!</string>
<string name="111968">You can only use assign mount with mounts owned by you or your henchmen.</string>
<string name="111969">You have released a mount.</string>
<string name="111970">You cannot release a mount unless it is assigned to you.</string>
<string name="111971">You selected a Mount twice and the second target should be a PC or NPC henchman.</string>
<string name="111972">Now use Assign Mount again to select which PC or Henchman the Mount should be assigned to.  NOTE: You can select this mount a second time to release it and remove it from your party.</string>
<string name="111973">You have assigned a mount to yourself.</string>
<string name="111974">You have given the mount to </string>
<string name="111975"> has given you a new mount.</string>
<string name="111976">You do not own that mount and cannot assign it.</string>
<string name="111977">You must use Assign Mount on a mount first and then on a PC or Henchman.</string>
<string name="111978">You gave a mount to </string>
<string name="111979">That henchman cannot ride that mount in their current state so, cannot have the mount assigned to them.</string>
<string name="111980">You must use Assign Mount on a mount first and then on a PC or Henchman.</string>
<string name="111981">Not a valid target.</string>
<string name="111982">You cannot shapeshift while mounted.</string>
<string name="111983">** You cannot mount that! **</string>
<string name="111984"> is already mounting that.</string>
<string name="111985">Unsummoned Paladin Mount.</string>
<string name="111986">Mounts are not allowed in this area.</string>
<string name="111987">You are already mounted on a paladin mount.</string>
<string name="111988">You already have a paladin mount.</string>
<string name="111989">Dismounting mounts first.  Entering the specified area mounted is not permitted.</string>
<string name="111990">Mounts are not allowed in the area you are entering so they will be left behind.</string>
<string name="111991"> used a mounted combat feat to avoid the damage from your last attack.</string>
<string name="111992">You used the mounted combat feat and a ride check to avoid damage from that last attack.</string>
<string name="111993">That target is dead!</string>
<string name="111994">You cannot mount another player.</string>
<string name="111995">Invalid rider specified.</string>
<string name="111996">You cannot mount an enemy mount.</string>
<string name="111997">You cannot mount that mount while it is being possessed by a DM.</string>
<string name="111998">Invalid rider. May not have a tail.</string>
<string name="111999">Invalid Rider.  This rider appears to be shape shifted.</string>
<string name="112000">The requested rider cannot ride this due to a race restriction.</string>
<string name="112001">The mount is assigned to another member of your party, or is owned by a non-party member.</string>
<string name="112002">You are not the owner of that mount and are not permitted to mount it.</string>
<string name="112003">Mounting is not permitted in this area.</string>
<string name="112004">Paladin mounts can only be mounted by their summoner.</string>
<string name="112005">The target is not a mount!</string>
<string name="112006">You cannot rest while mounted!</string>
<string name="112007">Castle Gate 2 (passage walkable)</string>
<string name="112008">Castle Wall (passage walkable)</string>
<string name="112009">Castle Wall Entrance (passage walkable)</string>
</resources>